Thank you.
ありがとう。
In the Sensai Academia Sinica, the knowledge-response lecture in May begins.
中央研究院では5月の知識応答講座が始まります。
Please start.
始めてください。
Thank you.
ありがとう。
Let's welcome 또An Jun's knowledge experience this month to all of you.
今月も또アンジュンの知識体験を皆さんにお迎えしましょう。
The jury personally from the graduate uzutian
卒業生ウズティアンから直接審査員
of Sheg suggestion Department of Roblox goodbye
Sheg の提案 Roblox 部門のさようなら
Dr. Wu Zhixiong graduated from the Department of Practice, National Taiwan University
Wu Zhixiong 博士は国立台湾大学実践学部を卒業しました。
Afterwards, he obtained a master's degree from the Institute of Biochemistry of National Taiwan University
その後、国立台湾大学生化学研究所で修士号を取得。
National Taiwan University Biochemistry is also co-organized with Academia Sinica
国立台湾大学生化学も中央研究院と共催
So it is also the Institute of Biochemistry of Academia Sinica
つまり、中央研究院生化学研究所でもあります。
Then joined the team of this biochemical institute to do research
その後、私はこの生化学研究所のチームに加わって研究をすることになりました。
Later came to the United States to study
その後アメリカに留学
Went to Wisconsin Medicine to get a Ph.D. in Medicinal Chemistry
医薬化学の博士号を取得するためにウィスコンシン大学へ進学
He was taught by the very famous Charles C.
彼は非常に有名なチャールズ C によって教えを受けました。
Then I returned to Taiwan and returned to the Institute of Biochemistry
その後台湾に戻り、生化学研究所に戻りました。
The Biochemical Institute was established here in 1995
生化学研究所は 1995 年にここに設立されました
The building that can be seen now
今見えている建物
At that time, Dr. Wu also moved to Academia Sinica
当時、呉博士も中央研究院に移った
So from the front in
それで正面から
After master's degree and after working as an assistant
修士課程修了後、助手を経て
be a researcher here
ここで研究者になる
43 years in total
通算43年
Now a so-called Special Review Researcher
現在はいわゆる特別審査研究員。
Research work without Boss
上司なしでの研究作業
Mainly the relationship between the structure and function of biochemical molecules
主に生化学分子の構造と機能の関係
Both small and large molecules
小さな分子も大きな分子も
e.g. proteoglycans
例：プロテオグリカン
Thinking of polysaccharides
多糖類を考える
Boss in fact
実は上司
An important field of research is Tang science
重要な研究分野は唐科学です
Let me tell you that Tang Science is actually a strong point of traditional Chinese medicine hospital
唐科学は実は中医学病院の強みだということを教えてください。
In fact, it is known in the world that the Chinese Medicine Hospital
実際、中医学病院は世界的に知られています。
is doing very well in this regard
この点では非常にうまくいっている
In the hospital of traditional Chinese medicine related to Tang Science
唐学関連の中医学病院内
number of researchers
研究者の数
should be in the world
世界にあるべきだ
When comparing in different universities
異なる大学で比較する場合
should be
あるべきです
It belongs to Saul, that is, the number of researchers who do Tang science
サウルに属する、つまり唐の科学を行う研究者の数
In this case, think about talking about this background
この場合、この背景について話すことを考えてください。
In the early days, Academician Chuan Li suggested to promote the scientific research of Tang Dynasty
初期の頃、学者の伝李氏は唐代の科学研究を促進することを提案しました。
He suggested Dr. Liu Deyong to be the director of the Institute of Biochemistry
彼は劉徳永博士を生化学研究所の所長に推薦した。
Then Director Liu also invited to work with Academician Chuan Li
その後、劉所長はまた、院士チュアン・リー氏と協力するよう招待した。
Japanese professor Jing Miao Enoe came to the Institute of Biochemistry to learn about it
日本の教授、エノエ・ジン・ミャオ氏は、それについて学ぶために生化学研究所に来ました
This is the beginning of some scientific research by Tang
これは唐による科学研究の始まりです
At the same time, some researchers
同時に、一部の研究者は、
Of course, later, after the head of Weng District Committee returned to Taiwan,
もちろんその後、汪区委員長が台湾に帰国した後、
It further promoted the research of Tang Science
唐学の研究をさらに推進した
It is also difficult for more researchers to invest in this area
さらに多くの研究者がこの分野に投資することも難しい
If nothing is lost, even in this field
この分野でも何も失わなければ
Be a Pioneer at Academia Sinica
中央研究院の先駆者になろう
started doing it very early
とても早くからやり始めた
The other question is that he gave some international organizations
もう一つの質問は、彼がいくつかの国際機関に与えたということです。
Also active is very involved
アクティブにも非常に関与しています
For example, he often participates in
たとえば、彼はよく次のようなイベントに参加します。
ACGG stands for Asian Community of Glycobiology
ACGGはアジア糖鎖生物学コミュニティの略です
Glycotechnology
糖鎖テクノロジー
And Cylo Glycobiology
そしてサイロ糖鎖生物学
Nesalogy is Tropic Acid
Nesalogy はトロピカル酸です
Our two societies are international societies
私たちの二つの社会は国際的な社会です
Also done in Taiwan
台湾でもやってた
Their knowledge should be the conference of the international society
彼らの知識は国際社会の会議になるはずです
The other thing to mention is that he is accepting
もう一つ言及すべきことは、彼は受け入れているということです
Professor InternetWay later
後でインターネットウェイ教授
It's a pity that he returned to Japan after retiring here
彼がここで引退して日本に戻ったのは残念だ
Died a few years later
数年後に亡くなった
Before his death, there was a request from Dean Li Quan, Dean Li
彼の死の前に、李泉学部長、李学部長からの要請がありました。
Dr. Wu Shixiong established this foundation for scientific research and education in Taipei City, Taiwan
呉世雄博士は台湾の台北市に科学研究と教育のための財団を設立しました。
He is currently the chairman of the foundation to promote scientific research and education in Tang Dynasty
彼は現在、唐代の科学研究と教育を促進する財団の理事長を務めています。
So he has many high achievements in research and education
研究や教育において多くの高い業績を残している
Today he will share with us the relationship between Tang powder quality and life in the way of popular science
今日、彼は唐粉の品質と生命の関係を大衆科学の観点から私たちに教えてくれます。
We welcome Dr. Wu
ウー博士を歓迎します
Thank you Vice President Li Wu for your introduction
李呉副社長、ご紹介いただきありがとうございます。
I have been in Academia Sinica for 43 years
私は中央研究院に43年間在籍しています
From the age of 65 this year, I entered the Institute of Biochemistry, Academia Sinica at the age of 22
今年65歳になり、22歳で中央研究院生化学研究所に入学しました。
At that time, the Institute of Biochemistry was at National Taiwan University.
当時、生化学研究所は国立台湾大学にありました。
until now i
今まで私は
Frankly speaking, I started doing it as a graduate student.
率直に言うと、私がこの仕事を始めたのは大学院生のときでした。
slowly do it now
今ゆっくりやってみよう
I will talk about this topic today
今日はこのテーマについて話します
The relationship between sugar molecules and life
糖分子と生命の関係
I divide this part into four parts
この部分を4つの部分に分けます
As soon as I get to the first part, I'll cover the basic sugar
最初の部分に到達したら、基本的な砂糖について説明します。
The second part will talk about the relationship between sugar and blood
後編では糖と血液の関係についてお話します。
Then the third part will talk about
続いて第 3 部では次のことについて話します
The relationship between sugar and infectious diseases
砂糖と感染症の関係
The last part of the fourth part is about
第4部の最後の部分は、
our food
私たちの食べ物
What does our healthy food have to do with sugar?
私たちの健康食品と砂糖はどのような関係があるのでしょうか?
Then I'm going to start with this sugary basic this one
それから、この甘い基本的なものから始めます
Let’s start with the basic chemical structure of sugar
砂糖の基本的な化学構造から始めましょう
Our body is roughly divided into five categories
私たちの体は大きく5つに分類されます
Materially speaking, we are really like eggs
物質的に言えば、私たちは本当に卵のようなものです
It is, of course, an enzyme
もちろん酵素です
Nucleic acid is genetic material
核酸は遺伝物質です
Our basic concept of sugar quality is
当社の糖品質の基本的な考え方は、
it is an energy, an energy it provides
それはエネルギーです、それが提供するエネルギーです
Fat is mainly related to cell membrane
脂肪は主に細胞膜に関係しています
Of course, there are many other functions, but they are more related to the cell membrane
もちろん、他にも多くの機能がありますが、それらは細胞膜に関連しています。
Then there are minerals, inorganic minerals
次にミネラル、無機ミネラルです。
Like calcium, magnesium, mushrooms, scales, scales, these are in fact a coordinating agent
カルシウム、マグネシウム、キノコ、鱗、鱗のように、これらは実際には調整剤です
Maybe these enzymes need these minerals to work
おそらくこれらの酵素が機能するにはこれらのミネラルが必要です
Sugar is more than energy
砂糖はエネルギー以上のものです
When it is oxidized, it turns into carbon dioxide
酸化すると二酸化炭素になります
Produce ATP, we know that ATP is energy
ATP を生成します。ATP はエネルギーであることがわかっています。
and structure
そして構造
You can see the fiber of some plants
いくつかの植物の繊維が見えます
It's just a structure, sugar, those fibers are sugar
それは単なる構造です、砂糖、それらの繊維はすべて砂糖です
and chitins
そしてキチン質
The value of a few kilograms is actually a structure
数キログラムの価値は実際には構造物です
The value of a few catties is also the sugar value
数斤の価値も砂糖の価値です
The third part is more complicated
3番目の部分はさらに複雑です
It can be used as a molecule for cell information transmission
細胞の情報伝達分子として利用可能
cell-to-cell contact
細胞間の接触
and your protein
そしてあなたのタンパク質
If you want to send to the synthesis
合成に送りたい場合
where to send
どこに送るか
It also has to have sugar to boot it
それを起動するには砂糖も必要です
we say basic sugar
基本的な砂糖と言います
Regular sugar like this is the basic
このような普通の砂糖が基本です
Its structure is that it's six carbons
その構造は炭素が6つあるということです
twelve hydrogen six oxygen
十二水素六酸素
But here we call it six-carbon sugar
しかし、ここではそれを六炭糖と呼びます
Of course there are five-carbon sugars and four-carbon sugars
もちろん五炭糖や四炭糖もあります。
But our most basic
しかし、私たちの最も基本的なものは、
just plain sugar
ただの砂糖
it's one you see this first
これは最初に見るものです
if it was a sugar
それが砂糖だったら
it has a property
それはプロパティを持っています
One of the most important features is the
最も重要な機能の 1 つは、
it easily turns into sugar
簡単に砂糖に変わります
it has fat and protein
脂肪とタンパク質が含まれています
egg white some protein is also very easy to water
卵白にタンパク質が含まれているため、水分補給も非常に簡単です
Some protein can also not easily water
一部のタンパク質は水分を吸収しにくいものもあります
like our hair is protein
私たちの髪の毛がタンパク質であるように
But our hair is not easy to water
しかし私たちの髪は水に濡れやすいものではありません
what about glucose
ブドウ糖はどうですか
and galactose
とガラクトース
and glucosamine
とグルコサミン
This is the OHG replaced by an amine group
これはアミン基で置換されたOHGです
our name is glucosamine
私たちの名前はグルコサミンです
and some dried sucrose
乾燥スクロース少々
a lot of salt algalose
たくさんのサリノース
Of course if there are some changes
もちろん多少の変更があれば
It is this alcohol that will be oxidized to acid
アルコールが酸化して酸になったものです
That's of course glucosinolate
それはもちろんグルコシノレートです
no matter what
何があっても
Sugar has a very basic
砂糖には非常に基本的なものがあります
It is itself at the first carbon
それ自体が最初の炭素です
it's a whole acid
それは全体の酸です
We'll talk about this later
これについては後で話します
There are two types of sugar
砂糖には2種類ある
Like if you look at glucose and fructose
ブドウ糖と果糖を見てみると
Fructose is much sweeter than glucose
フルクトースはブドウ糖よりもはるかに甘い
but in fact
しかし実際には
it is an isomer
それは異性体です
clearly see this glucose
このグルコースがはっきりと見えます
It is a full machine
フルマシンです
its on the first carbon
最初の炭素にあります
it's the whole machine
それはマシン全体です
what about fructose
フルクトースはどうですか
it's on the second carbon it's a copper
それは2番目の炭素にあり、それは銅です
so it's copper sugar
つまり銅砂糖です
That glucose is a whole sugar
そのグルコースは全糖です
the main difference
主な違い
Just in front of these two carbons
この 2 つの炭素のすぐ前に
Everything else is exactly the same
他は全く同じです
that sugar itself
その砂糖そのもの
you can see it in the water solution
水溶液中で見ることができます
We can draw it as beyond the chain
鎖の向こう側に描くこともできる
But what about in aqueous solution?
しかし水溶液では
About ninety percent or more
約9割以上
it will ease
それは楽になります
it will be more stable
より安定します
You can see it slowing down, how to slow it down?
速度が低下しているのがわかりますが、速度を低下させるにはどうすればよいでしょうか?
It's on the fifth carbon, what about the fifth carbon, what about this
5 番目の炭素にあります、5 番目の炭素はどうですか、これはどうですか
will come to attack the second carbon and then become a slow
2番目の炭素を攻撃するようになり、その後は遅くなります
This will be more stable
こっちの方が安定するよ
When it becomes slow and strong, this one
ゆっくり強くなるとこれ
The first one is the first one, what about the carbon that has the authority?
1つ目は1つ目ですが、権限のあるカーボンはどうでしょうか？
it will produce two solid shapes
2 つの立体形状が生成されます
You can see this OH this marked here
ここにマークが付いているのがわかります
It can be pictured below, or it can be pictured above
それは底のようなものかもしれないし、上のようなものかもしれない
This upward direction is what we call
この上向きの方向を私たちは呼んでいるものです
Upwards, we call it MEDA
上向きに MEDA と呼びます
down, we call it α
下、それをαと呼びます
This is mixed together, generally speaking
一般的に言えば、これが混在しています
MEDA is relatively stable
MEDAは比較的安定しています
So it is in the water, there will be more MEDA
だからそれは水の中にあり、もっと多くのMEDAがあるでしょう
What about this, remember this from now on
これはどうですか、これからはこれを覚えておいてください
As we'll see below, how important it is
以下でわかるように、それがどれほど重要であるか
this you see how important it is
これがいかに重要であるかがわかります
let's see
どれどれ
this is starch
これはでんぷんです
Starch it is αe4
でんぷん、それはαe4です
That is, it is a giant sugar
つまり巨大な砂糖です
It relies on αe4 such a direct
このような直接的なαe4に依存します
just saw this candy
このお菓子を見たばかりです
it this first oh it goes down
これが最初だ、ああ、それは下がる
The gradual formation of sugars is two OH
糖の段階的な形成は2つのOHです
take off a water
水を取り除く
H2O leaves one sugar for two
H2O は 2 つの砂糖に対して 1 つの砂糖を残します
leave an oxygen
酸素を残す
oxygen hand
酸素ハンド
Because oxygen is the hand of oxygen
酸素は酸素の手だから
go pick up these two egg candies
この 2 つの卵キャンディーを取りに行きます
That starch is αe4
そのデンプンはαe4です
fiber is βe4
繊維はβe4です
In fact fiber and starch
実は食物繊維とでんぷん
is the equivalent
同等です
But its properties are completely different
しかしその性質は全く異なります
Simply put, if we humans want to digest this starch, it is easy
簡単に言うと、私たち人間がこのデンプンを消化しようと思えば、それは簡単です。
But to digest fiber, it's not that hard
でも食物繊維を消化するのはそれほど難しくない
So generally speaking, if it is something alpha, it is probably easily digested in our stomachs
一般的に言えば、それがアルファのものであれば、おそらく私たちの胃の中で簡単に消化されるでしょう。
If you want fibers, you have to be like cows, horses, and sheep, which are anti-removal
繊維が欲しいなら、除去を妨げる牛、馬、羊のようにならなければなりません
It relies on the dimensional organisms in its four positions to decompose these fibers
これらの繊維を分解するために、4 つの位置にある次元有機体に依存しています。
But generally speaking, fiber, if it is, if it is Meta, Meta, it is more of a structural type
しかし、一般的に言えば、ファイバーは、もしそれがメタ、メタであれば、それはより構造的なタイプです。
It belongs to the category. If Alpha is a food type, the score will be slightly lowered, but not absolutely.
比較に属しますが、食べ物の種類であればスコアは若干減りますが、絶対にそうとは限りません
Then I just said that sugar is our source of energy
それから砂糖は私たちのエネルギー源だと言いました
What about us, if sugar, if glucose, a glucose, it will be broken down
私たちはどうでしょうか、砂糖なら、ブドウ糖なら、ブドウ糖なら分解されます
decompose into red acid
先分解成餅紅酸
First decompose into two cake red acid
最初に2つのケーキの赤い酸に分解します
Cake red acid is to make three carbons
ケーキの赤い酸は炭素を3つ作ることです
then come in
それから入ってください
if aerobic
有酸素なら
it produces a lot of
それはたくさんのことを生み出します
energy
エネルギー
That is the process
それがプロセスです
is to be in
にいるのです
inside the body
体の内側
do this
これを行う
under aerobic conditions
好気的条件下で
If
もしも
when there is no oxygen
酸素がないとき
if you go for a sun run
太陽のランニングに行くなら
Obviously I can't run anymore
明らかにもう走れない
no, because we probably
いいえ、おそらく私たちは
eight minutes ahead
8分前
if you are a frequent runner
あなたが頻繁にランナーであれば
about eight minutes ahead
約8分前
about as much dextrose as you can use
使用できる量のブドウ糖
run out
なくなる
It runs out in eight to ten minutes
8～10分でなくなります
not a player
選手ではない
So if you usually run
したがって、通常実行している場合は、
Then you want to run next
じゃあ次に走りたいのは
but no way
でも仕方ない
Your oxygen, oxygen replacement, and other abilities are very poor
酸素、酸素置換、その他の能力が非常に低い
you run the next day
次の日にあなたは走ります
wow, that's a good deal
うわー、それはいいことだよ
It's because of lactic acid, lactic acid at the end
乳酸のせいだよ、最後に乳酸
will harden it from your blood into your liver
血液から肝臓まで硬化させます
Resynthesized into glucose and reused
ブドウ糖に再合成して再利用
What about the other thing?
他のことはどうですか？
in the absence of oxygen
酸素がない状態で
it carries on this put
それはこのパットを引き継ぎます
the fermentation that takes place, the fermentation results in alcohol
発酵が起こり、その結果アルコールが生成されます。
Ah, if the control is not good
ああ、コントロールが悪いと
Alcohol is oxidized to acetic acid
アルコールが酸化されて酢酸になる
For the longest time, it was a thin line away from acetic acid.
長い間、酢酸と紙一重の関係でした。
what about the other one
もう一つはどうですか
I said sugar can be turned into structure
砂糖は構造物に変えることができると言いました
The most obvious is
最も明白なのは
Substance
物質
The so-called gelatin is derived from the original Xujing
いわゆるゼラチンは元の徐京に由来します
until
それまで
crab until
カニまで
crab shell shrimp shell insect
カニの殻 エビの殻 昆虫
this appearance
この姿
It's all base
それはすべてベースです
Butin is a polysaccharide
ブチンは多糖類です
It is also VEDA
それもヴェーダです
it is also
それも
Relying on this VEDA 1 4 this way again and again
この VEDA 1 4 に何度も何度も頼って
a linked polysaccharide
結合した多糖類
What about the only thing that's different about him?
彼の唯一違う点は何ですか？
He uses N and C glucosamine as a monomer
彼はモノマーとしてNおよびCグルコサミンを使用しています
If it's fiber, he's using glucose
食物繊維ならブドウ糖を使っていることになる
But this one uses N and C glucosamine as monomers
しかし、これはモノマーとしてNおよびCグルコサミンを使用しています
This is what you eat if you eat veggie
野菜を食べるならこれを食べる
I will talk about this later
これについては後で話します
So it can be used as a structure
構造物としても使えるので、
So the link is of this Beta E4 is mainly like fiber and a few cents.
つまり、この Beta E4 のリンクは主にファイバーと数セントのようなものです。
it's all structure
それはすべて構造です
There is one more concept I must convey to you first
最初に伝えなければならないコンセプトがもう 1 つあります
That is to say, you, this candy, you keep directing you, your α E4 E keeps directing and directing
つまり、あなた、このキャンディーはいつもあなたを導き、あなたのα E4 Eはいつもあなたを導きます
In fact he has his front and rear order
実際、彼には前後の順序がある
His 1, his first carbon is connected with his fourth carbon, connected together
彼の 1、つまり最初の炭素は 4 番目の炭素とつながっており、互いにつながっています。
For this, for this, his first carbon was originally
このために、このために、彼の最初のカーボンはもともと
His first carbon would have had a full product
彼の最初のカーボンは完全な製品になっていただろう
The whole product is oxidized, it becomes acid
製品全体が酸化し、酸性になります。
But, if you are a high school student, do you have any reaction now?
でも、高校生なら今何か反応ありますか？
If you have a reaction, do this
反応があったらこうする
Is your sugar reducing sugar?
あなたの砂糖は還元糖ですか？
What about this, this, this
これ、これ、これはどうですか
What about the one on the right, the one on the left, it is
右のものはどうですか、左のものはどうですか、それは
Disaccharides, the one on the left, we call them reducing sugars
二糖類、左側のものは還元糖と呼ばれます
It is because he is the first one, on the first carbon
それは彼が最初の人、最初のカーボンだからです
This is not used at all
これは全く使われていない
but this, this
でもこれ、これ
The one on the right and left is non-reducing sugar
左右にあるのは非還元糖です
So if one is very long, the other is
したがって、一方が非常に長い場合、もう一方は
it, if we re-transform, is on my right hand side
再変身したら右側にあるよ
my right hand side
私の右側
is the restore side
復元側です
The non-reducing end is always outside
非還元末端は常に外側にあります
That
それか
If enzymes break down sugar
酵素が糖を分解すると
it is uniform
それは均一です
almost uniform
ほぼ均一
non-reducing
非還元
inward action
往內作用
non-reducing end
非還元末端
Too
それも
closest outside
最接近外
close to the outermost
一番外側に近い
wait a minute we will
ちょっと待ってください。
talk about this
このことについて話してください
sugar
糖
it's not that simple
それはそれほど単純ではありません
just a single
たった一つだけ
it can
できる
correct
正しい
like starch
でんぷんのような
like this chitin
このキチンのように
like fiber
繊維のような
it can aggregate
集約できる
become a polymer
ポリマーになる
Polymer
ポリマー
very long molecule
非常に長い分子
just a glucose
ただのブドウ糖
it can be straight
まっすぐでもいいよ
It can be connected directly for a long time
長時間直接接続可能
sugar
砂糖
it
それ
can also
こともできます
with fat
脂肪付き
glycolipid
糖脂質が形成される
the fat
脂肪
We know that if a candy
キャンディーなら
This molecule just becomes a very strange
この分子は非常に奇妙なものになります
Because fat and sugar are incompatible
脂質と糖質は相性が悪いので
One is clear water, fat
一つはきれいな水と脂肪です
It is polyhydric
多価水素です
So you can see the two words together
したがって、2 つの単語を一緒に見ることができます
You can see that this substance becomes a bisexual substance
この物質は両性物質になることがわかります
Some of it is clear water, and some of it is water
一部は透明な水、一部は水
sorry, let me explain first
申し訳ありませんが、最初に説明させてください
because i'm not a philologist
私は文献学者ではないので
Nine characters, you can see a lot here
9 人のキャラクター、ここでたくさん見ることができます
I use nine useful rice and I mix it up
九合米を使用し混ぜます
Because I think the two are about the same
両者はほぼ同じだと思うので
Some would argue that the two are not the same
この二つは同じではないと主張する人もいるだろう
Some people say that you can also use the word "米" next to the things you fill in.
記入する項目の横に「米」を入れても良いという人もいます。
For things not to be filled in, he can also use the word Nine
埋められないものについては、「ナイン」という言葉も使うことができます。
But I'm not a philologist
でも私は文献学者ではありません
This may ask this to write text
これはテキストを書くように要求するかもしれません
text like the historical institute
歴史研究所のようなテキスト
protein it can also form elastic
タンパク質は弾力性を形成することもできます
Glycoprotein is very popular
糖タンパク質は非常に人気があります
What about our antibodies?
私たちの抗体はどうなるのでしょうか？
A lot of about 6-70% protein
たんぱく質が約6～70％多く含まれています
are glycoproteins
糖タンパク質です
I just said that after protein is modified with sugar,
タンパク質が糖で修飾された後、
so that our cells know
私たちの細胞が知ることができるように
Which fixed organ should it be sent to?
どの固定臓器に送るべきでしょうか？
Okay, I'm going to look at this now. This is a basic
さて、これからこれを見ていきます。これは基本です
The basic structure of the basic cell membrane
基本細胞膜の基本構造
Then you can see that this side is extracellular
すると、こちら側が細胞外であることがわかります
This is inside the cell
ここは細胞の中です
What is this sugar and fat?
この糖質と脂質は何でしょうか？
What about sugar and fat? Its fat part
砂糖と脂肪はどうですか?脂肪の部分
Just insert the whole thing on the membrane
全体を膜の上に挿入するだけです
It's exposed, it's a candy
露出してるよ、キャンディーだよ
oligosaccharide or polysaccharide fraction
オリゴ糖または多糖画分
This one by one is sugar
これは一つ一つが砂糖です
the outermost
一番外側の
Look at the outermost candy
一番外側のキャンディーを見てください
It is the non-reducing end
非還元端です
We are talking about the non-reducing end just mentioned
私たちは先ほど述べた非還元末端について話しています。
Then this is protein
じゃあこれはプロテインだ
this protein
このタンパク質
What about this water-accumulating spiral?
この水が溜まるスパイラルはどうなるのでしょうか？
It permeates the entire cell membrane
細胞膜全体に浸透します
Then the sugar part is also spread on the outside.
そして外側にも砂糖の部分を塗ります。
Whether you are glycoprotein or purple Tibetan white
あなたが糖タンパク質であろうと紫色のチベット白であろうと
You are on the membrane like this oil slick
膜の上にいると油膜はこんな感じ
The so-called cell membrane
いわゆる細胞膜
The cell membrane is of course formed by fat
細胞膜はもちろん脂肪によって作られています
This is a picture of a microscope of a cell membrane
これは細胞膜の顕微鏡写真です
you can see
見ることができます
Its whiskers are glycolipids
ひげは糖脂質です
Then this black string
するとこの黒い紐が
This is inside the fat cell
これは脂肪細胞の中にあります
this whole
この全体
this is the cell membrane
これは細胞膜です
What about the hee hee hee part?
ヒヒヒヒの部分はどうですか？
sugar
就是糖質
every cell
すべての細胞
it
それ
the appearance of these sugar
これらの砂糖の出現
what does it represent
それは何を表していますか
represent our faces
私たちの顔を表す
erythrocyte
紅血球
Will it be recycled in 190 to 120 days?
190～120日でリサイクルされるのでしょうか？
then we
それから私たち
how does the body recognize
身体はどうやって認識するのか
This red blood cell is
この赤血球は、
old red blood cells
古い赤血球
this is young
これは若いです
that is by
それはによる
This on the outside of this cell
これはこの細胞の外側にあります
this candy
このキャンディー
Cellular
携帯電話
sugar outside
外の砂糖
with healthy cells
健康な細胞とともに
The sugar outside is different
外の砂糖は違います
old and young
老いも若きも
sugar outside
外の砂糖
so i just said
だから私はちょうど言った
Glucose cost on the cell surface
細胞表面のグルコースコスト
different young
別の若い
cells are different from brain cells
細胞は脳細胞とは異なります
sick cells vs healthy cells
病気の細胞と健康な細胞
These sugars outside are not the same
外側にあるこれらの砂糖は同じではありません
If the blue part of this picture is the protein
この写真の青い部分がタンパク質だとすると
The yellow part is the sugar part
黄色い部分が砂糖の部分です
you can see
見ることができます
The protein part is very tight
プロテイン部分が非常にしっかりしている
won't move too much
あまり動かないでしょう
but the sugar part it can swing a lot
しかし砂糖の部分は大きく変動する可能性があります
That is, sugar molecules are easily fused with water.
つまり、糖分子は水と容易に融合します。
Having this sugar may have a lot to do with this protein
この糖の存在はこのタンパク質と大きく関係している可能性があります
protect it or many functions
それを保護したり、多くの機能を保護したりする
we'll talk about this later
これについては後で話します
So for a cell
したがって、細胞の場合
this is the nucleus
これが核です
Those outside are sugar
外側のものは砂糖です
or protein
またはプロテイン
That doesn't matter if your bacteria are coming
細菌が入ってきても関係ない
when attacking us
私たちを攻撃するとき
Sugar is the first thing
砂糖が最初です
Viruses come and go
ウイルスは行き来する
first to sugar
まずは砂糖へ
cancer cells to metastasize
がん細胞が転移する
he wants to transfer
彼は転校したいと思っています
cut this off
これを切り取る
and then he was able to run
そして彼は走れるようになった
Or the cancer cells are going to go to a place
それとも癌細胞がどこかに行くのか
to protect
守ること
he also depends on this
彼もこれに依存しています
sugar on top or
上に砂糖をかけたり、
some protein and
いくつかのプロテインと
These surrounding cells interact with each other
これらの周囲の細胞は相互作用します
Contact him to be here
彼にここにいるように連絡してください
Implantation grows
着床が成長する
become a cancerous tissue
癌性組織になる
that or your hormones
それかあなたのホルモン
you want to touch
触れたいですか
to stimulate
刺激する
to stimulate this cell
この細胞を刺激するために
met outside
外で会った
Possibly protein
おそらくタンパク質
or sugar
または砂糖
so
それで
what about this one
これはどうですか
is typical
典型的です
cell surface carbohydrate molecules
細胞表面的糖質分子
exchanging information with the outside world
外部との情報交換
important bridge of
の重要な橋
Now what, I have to tell you about a protein
さて、プロテインについて話さなければなりません
This protein is closely related to sugar
このタンパク質は糖と密接に関係しています
lectin
レクチン
What is lectin?
レクチンとは何ですか?
is that it is a protein
それはタンパク質であるということです
It is a protein or glycoprotein that can bind with sugar
糖と結合できるタンパク質または糖タンパク質です。
It can bind sugar
糖と結合する可能性がある
When two cells come together
2つの細胞が集まるとき
lectin
レクチン
Lectin is a protein
レクチンはタンパク質です
But its function is to combine with sugar molecules
しかし、その機能は糖分子と結合することです
that's how it is
それがその通りです
How does lectin combine with it
レクチンはどのように結合するのでしょうか
like you see this
これを見ているように
cold virus
風邪のウイルス
Either weak energy or some poison
あるいは弱いエネルギーか何かの毒
I will give an example later
後ほど例を挙げます
Lectin is a protein
レクチンはタンパク質です
The function of this protein is to combine with sugar molecules
このタンパク質の機能は糖分子と結合することです
Thanks
ありがとう
But the power of this spirit number combined with sugar molecules
でもこのスピリットナンバーの力は糖分子と組み合わされて
It's combined, this power is not going through the carpool
それは結合されている、この力は相乗りではない
That's what we call, it's a second class ship
いわゆる二等船です
That's the power you can't see
それは目に見えない力
you can measure it, but sometimes
測定することはできますが、場合によっては
You're probably thinking it's not a real chemical ship
おそらく本物の化学船ではないと思っているでしょう
Is it a clear ship or an ion ship
クリアシップかイオンシップか
or ring de valli , or the effect of polyhydricity
またはリング・デ・ヴァリ、または多水酸基の効果
Paste together, it will produce two and combine together
一緒に貼り付けると 2 つ生成され、結合されます
This power is not very strong, but
この力はそれほど強いものではありませんが、
Phenomena that have dominated our lives since the Lord
主以来私たちの生活を支配してきた現象
Both of these tell us that the combination of the number of spirits and sugar molecules
これらはどちらも、蒸留酒の数と糖分子の組み合わせによって次のことがわかります。
Relying on the power of this non-common ship
ありふれた船の力を頼りに
Kiyomi, positive and negative electricity attract together
清美、プラスとマイナスの電気が引き合う
what about this you can see
これはどうですか？
When a virus wants to enter our cells
ウイルスが私たちの細胞に侵入しようとするとき
There are some lectin on the virus
ウイルスにはレクチンが存在します
can bind to cellular sugars
細胞の糖に結合することができる
Or the cholera toxin
あるいはコレラ毒素
when it enters our cells
それが私たちの細胞に入ると
What about the toxin?
毒素はどうですか？
it also passes through
それも通過します
sugar that will stick to the cell first
最初に細胞にくっつく砂糖
or germs
または細菌
Lactobacillus
乳酸菌
it has a lot of this lectin
このレクチンがたくさん含まれています
It will also deactivate the lectin on the bacteria
細菌上のレクチンも不活性化します
will bind to this sugar on our cells
私たちの細胞上のこの糖に結合します
and then into our cells
そして私たちの細胞の中へ
sometimes like the most famous
時には最も有名なように
like white blood cells
像白血球
it's going to where we hurt
それは私たちが傷ついたところへ行く
escape from the blood vessels
血管から逃げる
what about this time
今回はどうですか
How does it focus on vascular
どのようにして血管に焦点を当てるのか
The first step also relies on lectin
最初のステップもレクチンに依存します
It's the urgency number on the maintenance tube that attracts it down
メンテナンスチューブの緊急番号がそれを引き寄せる
Then he'll run out to the injured area to fight the foreign intrusion
それから彼は外敵の侵入と戦うために負傷した場所に走り出すだろう
In fact, these are all related to our life and life.
実は、これらはすべて私たちの生活や人生に関係しています。
Therefore, it will be easier to talk about the following after the anxious number is finished.
そのため、気になる数字が終わってから次の話をすると話しやすくなります。
In order to let everyone have a better understanding of the number of jitters, let me give you an example
ジッターの数をより深く理解していただくために、例を挙げてみましょう。
Let me give you an example golden boar protein
ゴールデンボアプロテインの例を挙げましょう
Have you heard of golden boar protein? This is our academician Lin Rongrong who has done a lot of research
ゴールデンボアプロテインについて聞いたことがありますか?これは多くの研究を行ってきた私たちの学者、林栄栄です。
Golden boar protein is quite poisonous
ゴールデンボアプロテインは猛毒です
I remember playing with this a lot when I was a kid and its seeds
子供の頃、これとその種でよく遊んだのを覚えています
But it's actually quite poisonous in it
でも実はかなりの毒が含まれているんです
It has a kind of what we call golden boar protein in it
ゴールデンボアプロテインと呼ばれるものが含まれています
it has two
それは2つあります
Divide it into two parts, you see, it finances into the egg white and divides it into two parts
それを2つの部分に分けます、ほら、それは卵白に資金を与え、それを2つの部分に分けます
Part of it, let's say A, part of it
その一部、仮にAとしましょう、その一部
Let's call this blue A
これを青Aと呼びましょう
Let's call the part of this potential color B.
この潜在的な色の部分を B と呼びましょう。
A what is it? A is actually an enzyme
A それは何ですか? A は実は酵素です
it goes into
それは入ります
If it enters our cells, it will put
それが私たちの細胞に入ると、
protein-making machine, glycosome, inside
タンパク質製造機構、グリコソーム、内部
RNA breaks it down
RNAがそれを分解する
It's quite a lot, but what if
かなり多いですが、どうでしょうか？
only A, if you owe
借りがある場合は A のみ
only A words
たった一言
don't read it because it can't get into the cell
セルに入らないので読まないでください
In fact there are many plants that only contain A
実際、Aだけを含む植物はたくさんあります。
but not toxic
しかし有毒ではありません
It depends on B, what is B?
それはB次第ですが、Bとは何ですか？
B is that it is a lectin
Bはレクチンであること
A and B are connected by double arrows
A と B は二重矢印で結ばれています
B it will look for sugar on the cell surface
B 細胞表面で糖を探します
At once
すぐに
He is Ningji Sutu, after he combines with him
彼と合体するとニンジ・スートゥです。
If it is beneficial to A, enter
Aにとって有益な場合は入力してください
just go to this
ただこれに行ってください
enters the cells and becomes very toxic
細胞に入り込み、非常に有毒になります
This financial strain is actually very similar to that coin toxin
この経済的負担は実際にあのコインの毒素と非常によく似ています
One of the most famous cases was in 1978 when
最も有名なケースの 1 つは 1978 年に起こったものです。
A reporter from Eastern Europe lived after he escaped
東ヨーロッパ出身の記者が逃亡後に生き延びた
The British national broadcaster BBC is a reporter who has been bashing
英国国営放送BBCがバッシングしてきた記者
Bulgaria slams this Russia
ブルガリアがロシアを非難
Russia's KGB
ロシアのKGB
use this toxin
この毒素を使う
put it on top of this umbrella
この傘の上に置きます
Inject it into this guy while riding the subway
地下鉄に乗っている間にこの男に注射してください
At first he didn't know why he just said it was crowded
最初は彼はなぜ混雑しているとだけ言ったのか分かりませんでした
What about the toxin?
毒素はどうですか？
very fine
非常に細かい
Put it in a small iron ball
小さな鉄球に入れて
Just like that, after four days, he died
そのまま4日後に亡くなってしまいました
So this thing is actually very poisonous
つまり、これは実際には非常に有毒です
So I front these
だから私はこれらを正面に置きます
I'm done with the basics
基本的なことは終わりました
I'm going in now
今から入ります
I hope you will be more interested
もっと興味を持っていただければ幸いです
What I'm going to talk about next is related to academics
次にお話しするのは学問に関することです
some stories
いくつかの物語
bloody
血まみれの
There are mud blood, hematopoiesis, diabetes disease
泥血、造血、糖尿病などがあります
the blood
血
these stories
これらの物語
you see blood
血が見えます
bloody
血まみれの
If before 1900
1900年以前であれば
No one knows there is type A and there is type AB
A型とAB型があることは誰も知りません
O type
O型
Why
なぜ
will find out
分かるだろう
It's someone who survived a blood transfusion
輸血を受けて生き残った人です
Someone got a blood transfusion and died from the same blood transfusion
誰かが輸血を受け、同じ輸血によって死亡した
don't know
わかりません
1900, 24 seasons ago
1900年、24シーズン前
No one knows there is type A, there is type B, there is type AB, there is type O
A型があること、B型があること、AB型があること、O型があることは誰も知りません。
But what about the blood type here?
しかし、血液型はどうでしょうか？
It is formed on the surface of red blood cells
赤血球の表面に形成されます
This is a red blood cell.
これは赤血球です。
Glucose antigens on the surface to determine what blood type you are
血液型を決定する表面の糖抗原
you can see type o
O型が見えます
What about type O?
O型はどうでしょうか？
Glycoantigen here
糖抗原はこちら
Type A, there is one more
タイプA、もう一つあります
This quadrangular one is called galactosamine
この四角いのはガラクトサミンといいます
one extra
余分に1つ
so you type a
そこで、次のように入力します
What about blood type A?
血液型A型はどうでしょうか？
What about the antigen?
抗原はどうでしょうか？
O type no
O型いいえ
What about type O antigens?
O型抗原についてはどうですか？
Look at 1234, this type A is in the process of synthesis
1234を見てください、このタイプAは合成中です
There will also be O-type
O型もいるよ
So you type O lose to type A
つまりO型はA型に負ける
no problem
問題ない
Type A
A型
Type O you lose to Type A
O型はA型に負ける
Does a person with type A have type O antigens?
A型の人はO型抗原を持っていますか?
Type A and Type B cannot belong to each other.
タイプ A とタイプ B は互いに属することはできません。
Because type B has one more galactose than type O
B型はO型よりガラクトースが1つ多いため
In fact, type A and type B
実はA型とB型
one more galactose
もう一つのガラクトース
one is galactose
一つはガラクトースです
but this one is different
でもこれは違います
It’s just that the position where I painted Lanlan is different
ランランを描いた位置が違うだけです
It's just that the location is different
ただ場所が違うだけです
such a small difference
そんな小さな違い
You type A can't lose to type B
A型はB型に負けない
Type B can't lose to Type A
B型はA型に負けない
because it's what you typed in
それはあなたが入力したものだからです
it treats it as a foreign object
それを異物として扱います
Such a large amount of foreign matter comes in
こんなに大量の異物が入ってくるとは
that's worth it
それは価値がある
That person will probably be carbon off.
その人はおそらくカーボンオフになるでしょう。
So the blood transfusion was wrong
つまり輸血は間違っていた
will die
死んでしまいます
But type AB, he has both
でもAB型はその両方を持っている
Type AB, he also has type A
AB型だけどA型もある
Type B he also has
タイプBの彼もいる
Galactose also has
ガラクトースにも、
What about this, so you type A lose to type AB
では、A型はAB型に負けるということはどうでしょうか。
There is no problem losing to the AV type
AV系に負けても問題ない
it's all acceptable
それはすべて受け入れられます
So this is easy to see
なのでこれは見やすいですね
You type O can lose to any type
O型はどんなタイプにも負ける
But Type A except itself
ただし、タイプ A 自体を除く
It can also only lose to the AV type
AV系にも負けるしかない
it can't lose to type a either
a を入力しても負けません
Can't lose to V-type
V型には負けない
Like the V-type, it can't lose to the O-type
V型同様、O型にも負けない
Can't lose to Type A
A型には負けない
But it can lose to AV type
でもAV系には負けるかもしれない
AV type can
AVタイプ缶
But its main difference
しかし、その主な違いは
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
It is the surface of the red snowball
赤い雪玉の表面です
Glycoantigens to determine your studies
研究を決定するための糖抗原
then you will see in
そうすれば、あなたは見るでしょう
There was an article in 2007
2007年にこんな記事がありました
a biotech company
バイオテクノロジー企業
Did he say it was easy?
彼はそれは簡単だと言いましたか？
I put an enzyme
酵素を入れてみた
Cut off the A-type
Aタイプを切り捨てる
AV type this cut off
AVタイプこのカットオフ
Let's cut it all together and make it all O-shaped
全部切ってO字型にしましょう
someone did it
誰かがやった
He cut it off with enzymes and all the blood became type O
彼はそれを酵素で切断し、すべての血液がO型になった
It's very simple.
とてもシンプルです。
It's fine if you lose
負けても大丈夫
It was in 2007
2007年のことでした
There is an article in Nature about Technology
Nature にテクノロジーに関する記事があります
In this journal, he mentioned that
この日記の中で彼は次のように述べました
This is also a kind of biotechnology
これもバイオテクノロジーの一種です
Sometimes when there is a blood shortage
時々血液が不足するときがあります
You can't find this with this blood type
この血液型では見つかりません
They are all type B, so what should I do?
全員B型なんですが、どうしたらいいでしょうか？
You're also type B, you can't lose to him
あなたもB型、彼には負けられない
You can lose to him, but you can't lose to him
彼に負けることはあるが、彼に負けることはできない
At this time, take an enzyme and cut this off
この時、酵素をとってこれを切り取ります
It's very simple to say, but it should be built with a lot of technology
言うのは非常に簡単ですが、多くのテクノロジーを使って構築する必要があります
Okay, we're done with blood types, let's talk about this again.
さて、血液型については終わりました。これについてはもう一度話しましょう。
red blood cell count
赤血球数
What about red blood cell count?
赤血球数はどうでしょうか？
this initial poetic
この最初の詩的な
Let's call it epo for short.
略してエポと呼びましょう。
Chinese is called red blood cell production number
中国語では「赤血球生産数」といいます。
what about this epo
このエポはどうですか
what is
とは
because of U.S
米国のせいで
if blood stem cells
血液幹細胞なら
blood stem cells
血液幹細胞
it differentiates into red blood cells
赤血球に分化します
or it differentiates into white blood cells
あるいは白血球に分化する
or differentiate into platelets
または血小板に分化する
have to go through hormones
ホルモンを通過しなければならない
specific hormone destimulation
特定のホルモン脱刺激
specific hormone
特定のホルモン
then if it goes through
それが通過したら
If blood stem cells
血液幹細胞なら
in our bones
私たちの骨髄の中で
after release
リリース後
If by this epo
このエポジによると
red blood cell production
赤血球の生産
after stimulation it will
刺激後はそうなります
differentiate into red blood cells
赤血球に分化する
what about this
これはどうですか
What about the red blood cell count?
赤血球数はどうでしょうか？
where is it produced
どこで生産されていますか
mostly in our kidneys
主に腎臓にある
Produced in renal myocytes
腎筋細胞で生成される
Dialysis person
透析者
would not be able to generate enough
十分に生成できないだろう
epo blood
エポブラッド
So what about people who wash their kidneys?
では、腎臓を洗う人はどうなるでしょうか？
he will be very
彼はとてもそうなるだろう
very weak very tired
とても弱い、とても疲れている
Because he doesn't have enough red blood cells, he's anemic.
赤血球が足りないので貧血になっています。
anything else
他に何か
this
これ
In fact there is something like this
実はこんな事もあるんです
If the retarded man uses
知的障害のある男性が使用する場合
He will also be anemic with medication
薬を飲むと貧血にもなる
that is
あれは
not enough red blood cells
赤血球が足りない
at this time
現時点では
In this epo in 1989, he
1989 年のこのエポで、彼は
by US drug
アメリカの薬によって
What about the Food Administration, he will approve
食糧庁はどうだ、彼は承認するだろう
You can come and wash this kidney
この腎臓を洗いに来てもいいよ
to make him
彼を作るために
be able to have enough of this
これで十分になれるだろう
This red blood cell, so I injected this
この赤血球、だからこれを注射した
very good effect
とても良い効果
So let me see below
それでは以下を見てみましょう
he actually
彼は実際に
Epo is a glycoprotein
Epoは糖タンパク質です
green part
緑色の部分
you will see the green part
緑色の部分が見えます
just a protein
ただのタンパク質
the colored part
色の付いた部分
he has four
彼は4つ持っています
he has four candies
彼はキャンディーを4つ持っています
This one this one is sugar
これはこれは砂糖です
sugar chain sugar chain
糖鎖 糖鎖
so he is a glycoprotein
つまり彼は糖タンパク質です
he has four candies
彼はキャンディーを4つ持っています
those candies
それらのキャンディー
if
もしも
Our First Generation Biotechnology
当社の第一世代バイオテクノロジー
produced
生産された
just without sugar
砂糖を使わないだけで
What about this Epo without sugar?
砂糖を含まないこのエポはどうですか？
Hit the human body?
人体に当たる？
Useless
使い物にならない
But what about in the lab if you use cells
しかし、研究室で細胞を使う場合はどうなるでしょうか
It can work without hitting the human body
人体に当たらずに作業が可能
What does this mean?
これは何を意味するのでしょうか？
sugar
糖
these sweeteners
これらの甘味料
is protecting the protein
タンパク質を守っている
That is, if you don't have these sweeteners
つまり、これらの甘味料がなければ、
protect this outside
これを外で守る
Protein, Epo protein, when it hits the human body
プロテイン、エポプロテインが人体に入ると
It is easily broken down in the blood
血液中で簡単に分解されます
So Epo has glycoprotein
つまり、Epoには糖タンパク質が含まれています
The stability of this sugar in the human body is related to
人体内でのこの糖の安定性は次のことに関係しています。
There is a big biotechnology company in the United States called MGN
アメリカにMGNという大きなバイオテクノロジー企業があります。
It produced Epo, and because of Epo, it turned a large group
Epoを生み出し、Epoのおかげで大きなグループになった
Become a big factory of biotechnology
バイオテクノロジーの一大工場になる
In fact, the conversion of the Epo gene was done by Taiwanese Lin Fukun
実際、Epo遺伝子の変換は台湾人の林福君によって行われました。
I checked his, actually from 1975 to 1977
実際に1975年から1977年まで彼のことを調べてみた
All jobs at this hospital
この病院のすべての仕事
Epo has another story
エポには別の話があります
He was in the Blood Olympics in 2000
彼は2000年に血液オリンピックに出場した
declared banned
禁止を宣言された
Because the players need to bring more oxygen
選手たちはより多くの酸素を運ぶ必要があるため
so many people hit
とても多くの人がヒットしました
just hit a wave
ただ波に当たっただけ
Playing a wave has promoted a lot
ウェーブをプ​​レイすることでかなりの効果が得られました
He has more red blood cells than you
彼はあなたよりも多くの赤血球を持っています
I can run faster than you
私はあなたより速く走れます
because i have oxygen
酸素があるから
he will run faster than you
彼はあなたより速く走るでしょう
so why ban him
それでなぜ彼を禁止するのか
very dangerous
すごく危ない
What we people strive for is a balance
私たち人間が求めているのはバランスです
when you have too many red blood cells
赤血球が多すぎると
will cause blood
血の原因になります
high viscosity
高粘度
Stickier
より粘着性のある
then you'll break your heart
そうしたら君は心が壊れてしまうだろう
compression
圧縮
you a thing
あなたは何か
your blood is stickier
あなたの血液はもっとベタベタしています
your heart's last strength of course
もちろんあなたの心の最後の力
will increase
増加します
So some players get killed
それで殺されるプレイヤーもいる
It's because of a heart attack that will kill you
心臓発作で死ぬからだよ
So what about social technology?
では、ソーシャルテクノロジーについてはどうでしょうか？
can be used to save you
あなたを救うために使えます
can hurt you too
あなたも傷つける可能性があります
Technology is always neutral
テクノロジーは常に中立です
Next, let me say that it is also a kind of sugar-based medicine.
次に、これも砂糖を使った薬の一​​種であると言っておこう。
But this glycin is actually an anti-coagulation problem naturally produced in our body
しかし、このグリシンは実際には私たちの体内で自然に生成される抗凝固の問題です
have you ever donated blood
あなたは献血したことがありますか
What if your blood won't clot when you go to donate blood?
献血に行ったときに血液が固まらなかったらどうしますか？
Blood generally clots when it leaves the body
血液は通常、体外に出ると凝固します
If your blood leaves your body or yours then you have blood disease
あなたの血液があなたの体またはあなたの体から出た場合、あなたは血液疾患を患っています
your blood does not coagulate
あなたの血液は凝固しません
What about when you go to donate blood?
献血に行くときはどうでしょうか？
Anticoagulant blood will be put in the blood bag
抗凝固剤の血液が血液バッグに入れられます
For anticoagulation, there may be two types
抗凝固には 2 つのタイプがある
Sometimes it puts a citric acid
場合によってはクエン酸を入れることもあります
lower your pH
pHを下げる
glucosinolate
グルコシノレート
it's a sugar glycine in fact
それは実際にはシュガーグリシンです
Glucose is actually a sugar
グルコースは実際には砂糖です
It is a natural aggregation of this
これの自然な集合体です
is that it relies on sour sugar
それは酸っぱい砂糖に依存しているということです
A lot of sour sugar combined like this
たっぷりの酸っぱい砂糖がこんな感じで組み合わされています
a long long molecule
長い長い分子
a sugar molecule
一個糖分子
it can be used to treat
治療に使用できます
if you have surgery
手術を受けた場合
Deeper blood acid
より深い血液酸
The lungs also have blood acid, arterial acid, etc.
肺には血液酸、動脈酸などもあります。
and myocardial infarction
そして心筋梗塞
Because myocardial infarction is also the main
心筋梗塞もメインなので
But when glycin itself is used
しかし、グリシンそのものを使用すると、
There are two most feared side effects
最も恐れられている副作用は2つあります
If the amount used is difficult to control
使用量のコントロールが難しい場合
it causes internal bleeding
内出血を引き起こします
or your blood is harder to clot
あるいは血液が固まりにくくなる
Platelet function will decrease
血小板の機能が低下してしまう
This has happened to many
これは多くの人に起こりました
I know mainland China is separated from pigs or cows
中国本土が豚や牛から隔離されていることは知っています
That is also used in the human body in Gansu
甘粛省の人体にも使われているもの
that happened too
それも起こりました
How Gansu works
甘粛省の仕組み
make it blood anticoagulant
血液の抗凝固剤にする
It is so anticoagulant in nature
本質的に非常に抗凝固作用がある
we can find out
私たちは知ることができます
mosquitoes draw your blood
蚊があなたの血を吸います
If you go to fight mosquitoes
蚊と戦いに行くなら
bloody hands
血まみれの手
Mosquitoes have their own anticoagulants
蚊は本質的に抗凝血作用がある
draw your blood
血を抜きます
The water quality is also in the attraction
水質も魅力
In fact, many
実際、多くの
The mechanism of this protocol is actually a series of hydrolysis reactions of protein berry
このプロトコルのメカニズムは、実際にはタンパク質ベリーの一連の加水分解反応です。
These meringues are zero blood factor
このメレンゲは血液因子ゼロです
Protocols that lack either one may not be able to zero
どちらかが欠けているプロトコルはゼロ化できない可能性があります
If you can't zero in on which one are you missing?
焦点を絞ることができない場合、どれが欠けているのでしょうか?
Then if you lack it, there is no way for Zero Gu to become blood sick.
ならば、それが欠けていれば、ゼログが血病になるはずがない。
What about Gansu, its mechanism is that our human body has a protein
甘粛省はどうですか、そのメカニズムは私たち人間の体が持つタンパク質です。
I'm sorry, I don't know how to do this. I want to translate on my own, but I can't.
申し訳ありませんが、やり方がわかりません。自分で翻訳したいのですが、できません。
It is called antiso-min
アンチソミンといいます
by itself if alone
一人ならそれ自体で
It can be combined with this factor10A this can be combined with it
この係数と組み合わせることができます10A これと組み合わせることができます
But it is relatively weak, but once this protein is combined with glycin
しかし、それは比較的弱いですが、このタンパク質がグリシンと結合すると、
It can be combined with this factor10
この係数と組み合わせることができます10
become a hundred times stronger
百倍強くなる
Increase the binding force hundreds of times
結合力を数百倍に高める
So it's possible to block this
なのでこれをブロックすることも可能です
Block this cascade of protein berry hydrolysis reactions
プロテインベリー加水分解反応のこのカスケードをブロックします
So it can turn blood into Naya Gu
つまり血液をナヤ・グに変えることができるのです
The most efficient one right now is
現時点で最も効率的なのは、
The most effective is these five candies
最も効果的なのはこの5つのキャンディーです
The name of these five candies
この5つのお菓子の名前は
I can't find the Chinese name
中国語名が見つからない
terribly sorry
大変申し訳ありません
called fandopalinex
ファンドパリネックスと呼ばれる
It is a very strong anti-bleeding agent
非常に強力な抗出血剤です
Vice President Liu just said that
劉副大統領は先ほどこう述べた。
There are many sugar quality experts in our Chinese Academy
私たちの中国アカデミーには砂糖の品質の専門家がたくさんいます
Director of Genome Center
ゲノムセンター長
red top
紅上層
Director Hong is actually
実はホン監督は
it has
それは持っています
he studies this one
彼はこれを勉強します
this one
これです
This substance of the five halls
五堂のこの実体
He studies its synthesis
彼はその合成を研究しています
Research
研究的
It seems that there are many patents
特許もたくさんあるようです
It seems that they are planning to start a company to do this.
そのために会社を設立する計画があるようです。
In fact this thing
実はこの事
it can replace dry element
乾式要素を置き換えることができます
Then what
じゃあ何
If you after surgery
手術後の場合は
cause arterial thrombosis
動脈血栓症を引き起こす
it can be clear
それは明らかです
Then for acute coronary
次に、急性冠状動脈の場合
It is better than traditional dry vegetarian
従来のドライベジタリアンよりも優れています
this
これ
It is a very important medicine
とても大切なお薬です
now everyone wants to make it
今、誰もがそれを作りたいと思っています
synthesized
合成された
Then you can use many
そうすればたくさん使えます
not just medicine
薬だけではなく
Then when you donate blood, you can also put some
そうすれば、献血するときにも入れることができます
ok let's see now
さて、それでは見てみましょう
Diabetes mellitus this generation is also more
この世代でも糖尿病は増加しています
My blood sugar is also relatively high, so I pay more attention to this
血糖値も比較的高いので気を付けています
This diabetes disease is really scary
この糖尿病は本当に怖い病気です
Will your eyes be blind? Will your kidneys be damaged?
目が見えなくなったり、腎臓が損傷したりすることはありますか?
high blood sugar
他糖藥病血糖高
Why is it hurting so much? He hit all of this.
なぜそんなに痛いのですか? 彼はこれすべてを殴りました。
Organ why?
オルガンなぜ？
I just said he's a circular and straight lover
彼は循環的でストレートな恋人だと言いました
Straight love has a punch on it as long as there's a punch
まっすぐな愛にはパンチがある限りパンチがある
This is protein
これはプロテインです
If there is an amino group, he will box with the amino group.
アミノ基がある場合、彼はアミノ基とボックスします。
it's easy to become a suction test
吸引テストになりやすい
Just call up, it's okay to check
電話して確認するだけで大​​丈夫です
It's delicious, but it sucks if
美味しいけど、これだったらまずいよ
If it takes a long time, he will become a non-greasy, non-greasy word
時間が経てばベタベタしない言葉になる
What about the glycoprotein?
糖タンパク質はどうでしょうか？
It will be elasticized. If it is elasticized too much, it will gradually lose its function.
伸縮性がありますが、伸縮しすぎると徐々に機能が失われます。
Eyes will go blind if you drink
酒を飲むと目が見えなくなる
Drink A wine, you drink A wine, drink methanol
ワインを飲みなさい、あなたはワインを飲みなさい、メタノールを飲みなさい
Methanol becomes methanol in our body
メタノールは体内でメタノールになります
You drink, you alcohol, it's alcohol, it's okay
飲むんだよ、酒だよ、酒だよ、大丈夫だよ。
It's okay to drink methanol
メタノールは飲んでも大丈夫です
That's because, Yichun
それはイーチュンだからです
It can always be oxidized to acid
いつでも酸化して酸になる可能性がある
But methanol can only be oxidized to methanol
しかし、メタノールはメタノールにしか酸化できません
Methanol is so poisonous, why?
メタノールはとても有毒ですが、なぜですか?
Because it is the total product
トータル商品ですので
With full product, you can beat any egg white
完全な製品を使用すると、どんな卵白でも泡立てることができます
So drink alcohol, methanol, you will go blind
だからアルコールやメタノールを飲むと目が見えなくなるよ
That's the whole problem
それがすべての問題です
Methanol, mainly the total product
メタノール、主に全生成物
so you can see
それでわかります
If diabetes is sick, because we human beings
糖尿病が病気なら、それは私たち人間だからです
I just talked about protein, it has a certain
先ほどプロテインについて話しましたが、プロテインにはある特徴があります。
If your protein is old, it will be recycled
タンパク質が古い場合はリサイクルされます
If your protein recovery rate is greater than
タンパク質回収率が
Destruction rate Your protein will be destroyed
破壊率 あなたのタンパク質は破壊されます
Then you are normal, you are normal
それならあなたは普通です、あなたは普通です
But what if you get sick from diabetes?
しかし、糖尿病になったらどうなるでしょうか？
Because of you, your destruction rate
君のせいで君の破壊率は
bigger than this
これより大きい
recycling rate that
リサイクル率は
then you just
それならあなたはただ
no way, you are
まさか、あなたは
like us at my age
私の年齢の私たちのように
if compared with younger
年下と比べたら
My Protein Recovery Rate
私のタンパク質回収率
far inferior to you young man is
あなたよりはるかに劣った若者は
All aspects of him are comparisons
彼のあらゆる側面は比較対象的だ
Recycling rate, regeneration
リサイクル率、再生
This recycle we all
このリサイクルは私たち全員で行います
The so-called recycle is stronger
いわゆるリサイクルが強い
well there like
まあ、そこにあるような
Medication for type 2 diabetes like these
2型糖尿病の治療薬はこんな感じ
This drug is of course a sugar molecule.
この薬はもちろん糖分子です。
He is the will to decompose the beauty of starch
彼はデンプンの美しさを分解する意志です
It's all about decomposing starch
でんぷんを分解することがすべてです
just suppress it
ただそれを抑制するだけ
Now we break down the brow is what we call
今、私たちは眉を分解することを私たちが呼んでいるものです
Alpha Valley Sides
アルファバレーサイド
so suppress it
だからそれを抑制する
what about this
これはどうですか
Most of this medicine is what you eat
この薬のほとんどは食べたものです
food money
食費
eat in a few minutes
数分以内に食べる
So the medication for type 2 diabetes
つまり、2型糖尿病の治療薬は
some are also
いくつかもあります
molecules of sugar
糖の分子
Okay, so now I'm going to tell you a story about this infectious disease.
さて、今回はこの感染症についてお話します。
Infectious diseases are actually the same in all countries
感染症は実はどこの国でも同じ
Encountered an infectious disease
感染症に遭遇した
The policy of the first country is like this
第一国の政策はこんな感じ
The most important thing to fight is the cold
一番大事なのは風邪です
The first one was terrible because of the cold
最初は寒くて大変でした
historically horrible
歴史から見ても恐ろしい
let's see
どれどれ
this is in
これは入っています
This picture happened in the United States in 1918
この写真は 1918 年に米国で起こった
just the first time
初めてだけ
when the world war is coming to an end
世界大戦が終わりに近づいたとき
Spanish tourism at this time
この時期のスペインの観光業
Invasion of the world is in the hands of the United States
世界侵略はアメリカの手中にある
this time
この時
Hospitals, businesses, cities are all infected
病院、企業、都市はすべて感染している
So at that time
だからその時は
It was March 1918
1918年3月のことでした
This sense of tourism but living in the United States to see women's health in Saz State
米国に住んでいるのにサズ州の女性の健康を観察するという観光感覚
Then slowly expand to every corner of the world
そしてゆっくりと世界の隅々まで広がっていきます
At that time from March 1918 until June 1920
当時は1918年3月から1920年6月まで
I don't know why it disappeared
なぜ消えたのか分かりません
But at least 20 million people died
しかし少なくとも2000万人が亡くなった
this is horrible
これはひどいです
Some even say hundreds of millions
数億とも言う人もいます
close to 100 million
1億近く
At that time, medical technology was not so advanced.
当時は医療技術もそれほど進んでいませんでした。
But back then, people's brains were pretty powerful.
しかし当時、人々の脳は非常に強力でした。
He used the patient's specimen with spicy
彼は患者の検体をスパイシーなものとして使用した
Crazy save
クレイジーセーブ
After hot crazy save
ホットクレイジーセーブ後
So, in 2004, scientists reconstructed this flu virus
そこで 2004 年、科学者たちはこのインフルエンザ ウイルスを再構築しました。
Proved he was a H1N1 flu
彼がH1N1インフルエンザであることが証明された
I'm going to talk about what is H and what is N
私が話したいのはHとNについてです
I saw it in your report.
あなたのレポートで見ました。
HN H1N1 what is H what is N
HN H1N1 Hとは何ですか Nとは
I'm going to talk to you about this now
これからこのことについてお話します
What is H?
Hって何ですか？
H is sialyl lectin
Hはシアリルレクチンです
Its name is Hemagutinin
その名はヘマグチニン
it is a lectin is a protein
それはレクチンです、それはタンパク質です
is a protein on the surface of cold viruses
風邪ウイルスの表面にあるタンパク質です
N is sialidohydrolase
Nはシアリドヒドロラーゼです
its a beer sugar
それはビールの砂糖です
beer is sugar with beer
ビールはビールには砂糖が入っている
The acid is almost gone forever, forever at the ring end of the flying ring
酸はほぼ永遠に消え去ってしまう、フライングリングのリングエンドでは永遠に
That is, the outermost part of the cell sugar
つまり、細胞の糖の一番外側の部分です。
So when the lectin of the virus suddenly ran to our respiratory tract
ウイルスのレクチンが突然私たちの気道に侵入したとき
The first thing that happened was he went to the stripper again and glued it on
最初に起こったことは、彼が再びストリッパーのところに行き、それを接着したことです
So stick it on, this is the first step for the cold virus to enter the cell
だからこれを貼ってください、これが風邪ウイルスが細胞に侵入するための最初のステップです
It's a lectin. As I just said, lectin can bind to sugar.
それはレクチンです、今言ったように、レクチンは糖と結合することができます。
It's going to find it, it's a protein, it's in the cold virus
それはそれを見つけるでしょう、それはタンパク質です、それは風邪ウイルスの中にあります
These are proteins on the outside of the cold virus and genetic material on the inside
これらは風邪ウイルスの外側にあるタンパク質と内側にある遺伝物質です。
Its genetic material is RNA not DNA it is RNA
その遺伝物質はDNAではなくRNAです、それはRNAです
Outside, there are two very important proteins
外には 2 つの非常に重要なタンパク質があります
One is H which is the lectin of dehydrating acid
1 つは H で、脱水酸のレクチンです。
one is N
1人はNです
N is a dehydrating acid hydrolase
N は脱水酸加水分解酵素です
This is the H?
これはHですか？
This protein is used to enter cells
このタンパク質は細胞に入るために使用されます
The N is to leave the virus after soaking into the cells
Nはウイルスを細胞に浸透させた後に残すこと
After copying, when it is about to leave
コピー後、出発するとき
Use N to cut off the dehydrating acid
N を使用して脱水酸を遮断します。
Cut off the dehydrating acid it's of course fine
脱酸性の酸をカットしてください、もちろん大丈夫です
Otherwise, I'll tell you later
それ以外の場合は、後でお知らせします
What is the use of this and what is the use of these two
これは何の役に立つのか、この 2 つは何の役に立つのか
This is dehydrating acid
これは脱水酸です
What about dehydrating acid? I just talked about it.
脱水酸についてはどうですか? それについては先ほどお話しました。
Glycolipid molecules usually on the outside of cells
通常は細胞の外側にある糖脂質分子
And it's at the reducing end of the lung, which is the outermost
そしてそれは肺の最も外側にある縮小端にあります
So what about cold viruses like ours
では、私たちのような風邪ウイルスはどうでしょうか
Cold virus comes from our respiratory tract
風邪ウイルスは私たちの気道から来る
nose, this, this
鼻、これ、これ
as soon as it comes
来たらすぐに
Check for dehydrating acid, if there is, it sticks
脱水酸の有無を確認します。存在する場合は固着します。
ok look at this picture
わかりました、この写真を見てください
When this H, there are a lot of H outside, this is a virus.
このH、外でHが多いと、これはウイルスです。
What about the virus, it found us, this, this is a human cell
ウイルスはどうですか、ウイルスは私たちを見つけました、これは人間の細胞です
Viruses are of course much smaller than human cells
もちろんウイルスは人間の細胞よりもはるかに小さい
But it's the first one, it's attached to this dehydrating acid
でも、それは最初のものです、この脱水酸に付着しています
It's attached to this dehydrating acid. Look for it.
この脱水酸に付着しているので探してください。
Then it slowly enters our cells
それからゆっくりと私たちの細胞に入ります
When it enters the cell, it controls our entire cell
それが細胞に入ると、細胞全体を制御します
Tell our cells to do a lot of confinement of this cold virus
私たちの細胞にこの風邪のウイルスをたくさん閉じ込めるように指示してください
It will do a lot, become controlled by it, and do it all
それは多くのことを行い、それに支配されるようになります。
And then break down the cell
そして細胞を破壊する
Spread the power of this virus out
このウイルスの力を拡散させてください
to infect more cells, so we'll produce
より多くの細胞に感染するため、
When it is about to leave, this N I just mentioned
出発するとき、先ほど言ったこの N
It is a hydrolase of lyrenic acid
リレン酸の加水分解酵素です
It will cut the cell above it and cut it off
その上のセルを切断して切断します
Otherwise it won't get out it will stick to this
そうしないと抜けません、これにくっついてしまいます
This production of our cell breakdown
この細胞の破壊の生成
it's glued on so it won't get infected
接着してあるので感染しません
So this N, so H and N are related to torenic acid
つまり、この N、つまり H と N はトレン酸に関連しています。
One, H is the rapid number of torenic acid
1、H はトレン酸の急速な数です。
It can stick to it. N is the hydrolase of the acid
N は酸の加水分解酵素です
We all know that we know about the gag flu
インフルエンザについては誰もが知っていることを知っています
People who have taken the flu have heard that it is very effective
インフルエンザにかかった人は、とても効果があると聞いています。
In fact, if you eat it on the real machine, your cold will heal very quickly.
実際、実機で食べると風邪がすごく早く治ります。
Why
なぜ
But what is the flu?
しかし、インフルエンザとは何でしょうか？
What about the flu?
インフルエンザはどうですか？
it is
それはです
What about the flu? It's a cold virus.
インフルエンザはどうでしょうか? それは風邪のウイルスです。
This N is an enzyme
このNは酵素です
This N is an enzyme that hydrolyzes stripping acid
このNは剥離酸を加水分解する酵素です
its inhibitor
その阻害剤
It suppresses the function of this N
このNの働きを抑制します
Reduce the ability of the virus to spread
ウイルスの拡散能力を低下させる
It can be seen that the gram flu is
グラムインフルエンザは
Rosu medicine
Rosu藥腸
it is eaten
それは食べられます
what about the other one
もう一つはどうですか
What about another medicine?
別の薬はどうですか？
Gran vegetarian sausage
グランベジタリアンソーセージ
it is sprayed
それはスプレーされます
It's because the medicine is like this
薬がこうだから
If your medicine is too watery
薬が水っぽい場合
eat it
それを食べる
It didn't take long to get rid of it
それを取り除くのにそれほど時間はかかりませんでした
you eat
あなたは食べる
B vitamins are water soluble
ビタミンB群は水溶性です
you eat for about a few hours
数時間ほど食べます
It's yellow when you pee
おしっこすると黄色いです
This is clear water
これは澄んだ水です
So stay longer
だからもっと長くいてください
You need to be more watery
もっと水分を多く含む必要がある
passenger flu
乗客のインフルエンザ
This whole structure is relatively water-accumulating
この構造全体は比較的水が蓄積されています
it can be eaten
食べられるよ
This water is relatively strong
この水は比較的強いです
it is sprayed
それはスプレーされます
let's see
どれどれ
If there is guest flu
ゲストにインフルエンザが発生した場合
it puts N
Nを入れます
this N
このN
when its function is inhibited
その機能が阻害されると
if you don't have guest flu
ゲストがインフルエンザに罹っていない場合
you can see
見ることができます
This is a little bit dark
こちらは少し暗いです
It's a little dark
少し暗いです
cold virus
風邪のウイルス
it's in this cell
それはこの細胞の中にあります
keep growing
成長し続ける
Then what
じゃあ何
grow to the end
最後まで成長する
burst this cell
この細胞を破裂させる
And then put it in the particles of this cold virus
そしてそれをこの風邪ウイルスの粒子の中に入れます
Micro force spreads out
微小な力が広がる
to infect more cells
より多くの細胞に感染するために
at this time
現時点では
if you have gram flu
グラムインフルエンザに感染している場合
it can't put
それは置けない
When the stripping acid is cut completely
剥離酸が完全に切れたら
you can see
見ることができます
you see a lot
たくさん見ていますね
cold granules
冷たい顆粒
cold particles are
冷たい粒子は
caught in these cell membranes
この細胞膜に捕らえられて
broken cell membrane
壊れた細胞膜
you can see
見ることができます
With the flu and without the flu
インフルエンザがある場合とない場合
this is no gram flu
これはグラムインフルエンザではありません
its difference
その違い
they mean
彼らは意味します
if you have the flu
インフルエンザにかかっている場合
the gram flu you eat
あなたのグラムインフルエンザ
The spread rate of this cold
この風邪の蔓延率は
will be halved
半分になります
or at least 40% off
または少なくとも40％オフ
At this moment
この瞬間に
it goes infected
それは感染する
capacity of other cells
他のセルの容量
will be greatly reduced
大幅に削減されます
good
良い
I will re-enter now
今から再入場します
another subject
別の主題
is nosocomial infection
院内感染
What about nosocomial infection? You see the hospital.
院内感染はどうですか? 病院を受診します。
The hospital is disinfected every day
院内は毎日消毒を行っております
Then, what about the patients? Patients from all over the place went in again with bacteria.
では、患者はどうなったのかというと、各地から患者が細菌を持って再び来院しました。
Disinfect again
再度消毒
So the sick hospital is a nursery
つまり、病気の病院は保育園です
In a place where superbugs are grown
スーパーバグが育つ場所で
What are superbugs?
スーパーバクテリアとは何ですか？
is that it is a multi-drug resistant
それは多剤耐性があるということです
multidrug resistant bacteria
多剤耐性菌
It's when your antibiotics are initially effective
抗生物質が最初に効果を発揮する時期です
The more you use it, the less effective the more you use it
使えば使うほど効果が薄れる
So nosocomial infection is a very scary
院内感染はとても怖いです
It's like talking about Staphylococcus aureus bacteria, Lilong infection bacteria
黄色ブドウ球菌、リロン病について話しているようなものです
Or S. pneumoniae, a bunch of bacteria.
または Streptomyces pneumoniae、細菌の集団
those
それらの
Some bacteria are very poisonous and some bacteria are actually not very poisonous
非常に有毒な細菌もあれば、実際にはそれほど毒性のない細菌もいます
But what about older people?
しかし、高齢者はどうでしょうか？
or people with chronic diseases like diabetes
または糖尿病などの慢性疾患のある人
people with weak immunity
免疫力が弱い人
Once he got to the hospital it was easy
病院に行ってしまえば簡単だった
This is the high risk group
これはハイリスクグループです
These superbugs or multi-drug resistant bacteria
これらのスーパーバグまたは多剤耐性細菌
it's easy to find him
彼を見つけるのは簡単です
it will be like this
このようになります
to the hospital
病院へ
The hospital is not a place of intersection
病院は交差点ではありません
don't go
行かないでください
if you are not sick
あなたが病気でないなら
if you must go
行かなければならないなら
when you come out
あなたが出てきたとき
be sure to wash your hands
必ず手を洗ってください
Washing hands is one of the best defenses
手を洗うことは最善の防御策の一つです
Or you wear a mask and wash your hands
もしくはマスクをして手を洗いましょう
that's all the best
それが何よりです
nosocomial infection
院内感染
people have predictions
人には予言がある
like good
いいね
this
これ
The economist two years ago said
2年前の経済学者はこう言った
These multi-drug resistant things
これらの多剤耐性のもの
This creates a medical crisis for humanity
これは人類に医療危機をもたらす
use it as a cover
カバーとして使用します
He said
彼は言った
this
これ
multidrug resistant bacteria
多剤耐性菌
you to the end
あなたは最後まで
No
いいえ
can't find
見つからない
kill him
彼を殺せ
He not only reports
彼は報告するだけではなく、
like the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has also reported
米国疾病予防管理センターも報告しているように
For these multi-drug resistant
これらの多剤耐性に対して
he also has a report
彼も報告書を持っています
The weekly newsletter of the American Chemical Society
アメリカ化学会の週刊ニュースレター
He also reported this as a cover
彼はこれをカバーとしても報告しました
both years ago
どちらも年前
people are aware of the crisis
人々は危機を認識している
if an elderly person goes to the hospital
高齢者が病院に行ったら
What if you are
もしあなたがそうならどうしますか
Who are you
あなたは誰
The cancer patient is better or your other patients are better
がん患者の方が優れている、または他の患者の方が優れている
to the end
最後まで
In fact, many, probably more than half of the people
実際、多くの人、おそらく半数以上の人が、
all died of sepsis
全員が敗血症で死亡した
nosocomial infection
院内感染
septicemia
敗血
What is septicemia
敗血症とは
Septicemia is when bacteria get into your blood
敗血症は細菌が血液中に侵入することです
in charge
担当
and make you inflamed blood
そして血液が炎症を起こします
blood inflammation
血液の炎症
Then what
じゃあ何
will be yours
あなたのものになります
Because your immune system is weak, you will be infected
免疫力が低下しているので感染してしまう
blood to
血に
What about invading bacteria? Will it cause inflammation?
細菌が侵入すると炎症を引き起こすのでしょうか?
to take charge so that in the end it is
最終的にそうなるよう責任を負う
Light exhaustion, or something, just die
軽い疲労か何かで死んでください
This is a very serious medical issue
これは非常に深刻な医学的問題です
What causes sepsis is
敗血症の原因は、
There are some bacteria, some bacteria
細菌もいるし、細菌もいる
polysaccharide
多糖類
This is liver sepsis. In fact, it is also related to
これは肝敗血症ですが、実は次のようなことにも関係しています。
sugar related
砂糖関連
So how do we solve the problem of nosocomial infection?
では、どうすれば院内感染の問題を解決できるのでしょうか？
I think we can find new antibiotics
新しい抗生物質が見つかると思う
Dean Weng recently had a paper
ディーン・ウェンは最近論文を発表しました
well done if you are in
入っているならよくやった
The cover of our campus Zhongyuan Hospital
私たちのキャンパス中原病院の表紙
he saw
彼は見た
he develops new
彼は新しいものを開発する
new antibiotics
新的抗生素
antibiotic
抗生素的
you use
あなたが使う
He'll be resistant right away
彼はすぐに抵抗するだろう
Therefore, many pharmaceutical companies are not willing to develop
したがって、多くの製薬会社は開発に積極的ではありません。
Because his cycle is too fast
周期が早すぎるから
other profits
その他の利益
development is difficult
開発は難しい
but
しかし
Xu Jun is smarter than you
Xu Junはあなたより賢いです
Hsu Jun wants to be a few generations later
スー・ジュンは数世代後になりたい
He will be resistant to your antibiotics, and he will come out.
彼はあなたの抗生物質に耐性があり、出てくるでしょう。
another one?
もう一つ？
You need to bring your own preventive vaccines
予防ワクチンを自分で持参する必要があります
otherwise you will
そうでなければそうするだろう
prevention
防止
I think
私が思うに
Prevention of residual treatment
処理残存防止
So I am more inclined to make vaccines
だから私はワクチンを作ることにもっと興味がある
what is the vaccine for
何のためのワクチンですか
sugar required
要糖質
It's the superficial appearance
それは表面的な外観です
polysaccharide
多糖類
used as an antigen
抗原として使用される
make a vaccine
ワクチンを作ろう
you
あなた
Glucose antibiotics are now on the market
ブドウ糖系抗生物質が市販されています
As for vaccines, the most famous one is that we don’t care about others.
ワクチンに関して最も有名なのは、「他人のことは気にしない」ということです。
Let's take a look at the pneumococcal vaccine.
肺炎球菌ワクチンについて見てみましょう。
Was Taipei City in October or December last year?
台北市は去年の10月か12月でしたか？
That is, if you are 65 years old, you can get the pneumococcal vaccine, right?
つまり、65歳なら肺炎球菌ワクチンを受けられるということですね。
I used to be 75 years old, all of Taiwan
私はかつて75歳で、台湾全土でした。
like last year 2001
昨年の2001年のように
this taipei city
この台北市
From October to December, as long as there are four people over 65 years old in Taipei
10月から12月まで、台北市内に65歳以上の人が4人いる限り
You can subsidize a shot of 23 pneumococcal vaccines
23 種類の肺炎球菌ワクチンの接種を補助できます。
There are 23, there are 13, what is the difference?
23もある、13もある、違いは何ですか？
Right? Pneumonia streptoscopic
そうですか? 肺炎レンサ球菌検査
I should go for a phone call, if I accidentally get hospitalized at my age
この歳でうっかり入院してしまったら、電話をしに行くべきです
If I get pneumonia streptoscopic
肺炎になったらレントゲン検査を受けたら
Then maybe I'm miserable too
そうすると私も不幸になるかも知れません
What is it? It says 23 are Streptococcus pneumoniae polysaccharide vaccines
それは何ですか? 23 は肺炎球菌多糖体ワクチンだと書かれています
Those 13 are Streptococcus pneumoniae vaccines
この13種類は肺炎球菌ワクチンです
What is the full name Conjugated pneumococcal vaccine
正式名称は何ですか 結合型肺炎球菌ワクチン
If I tell you like this, will you hear me?
こんなこと言ったら聞いてくれる？
ok then let me explain why
わかりました、ではその理由を説明しましょう
What is what is a polysaccharide vaccine
多糖体ワクチンとは何ですか
What is a conjugate vaccine
結合型ワクチンとは何ですか
I explain to you
私はあなたに説明します
As I just said, bacteria have a layer of polysaccharides on their surface
先ほども言いましたが、細菌の表面には多糖類の層があります。
If we do our research
私たちが研究をすると
This polysaccharide will be separated and purified
この多糖類を分離精製します
superficial without damaging cells
細胞を傷つけることなく表面的に
don't break the cells
細胞を壊さないでください
It is the polysaccharide on the surface that purifies it
それを浄化するのは表面の多糖類です
This is the polysaccharide on the surface I am now
これが今の私の表面多糖体です
Okay, what about the 23rd one? The purified polysaccharides are just shot directly.
では、23 番目はどうでしょうか? 精製された多糖類を直接ショットするだけです。
hit you directly
あなたを直撃する
Of course they must have done some evaluation.
もちろん一定の評価は行っているはずだ。
Doing that will cause a funeral, it’s not as simple as what I said
そんなことしたら葬式になるよ、言ったほど簡単じゃないよ
What are the 13 companies?
13社とは何ですか？
13 is the one who wants the polysaccharide
13は多糖類が欲しい人です
connect him to this carrier
彼をこの通信事業者に接続します
This carrier is protein
この担体はタンパク質です
attached to this carrier
このキャリアに取り付けられている
This polysaccharide should be connected to this sugar
この多糖類はこの糖と結合しているはずです
Anyway, this sugar is an antigen
とにかく、この糖は抗原です
No matter if you use polysaccharide to make it or you connect it to a protein carrier to make it
多糖類を使用して作成するか、タンパク質キャリアーに接続して作成するかは関係ありません。
your major antigen
あなたの主要な抗原
These are the antigens that produce antibodies
これらは抗体を産生する抗原です
sugar
糖
You only need to connect to this protein
このタンパク質に接続するだけで済みます
They are called conjugate vaccines
それらは結合型ワクチンと呼ばれます
what's the difference between these two
この2つの違いは何ですか
sorry it's complicated
申し訳ありませんが、複雑です
but i simplified it
しかし私はそれを単純化しました
If you are a multiple
複数の場合
when the vaccine
ワクチンのとき
Dodo when the vaccine
ワクチン接種時のドードー
you may
してもいいです
your efficiency is short
効率が足りない
The most important thing for us to vaccinate is to
私たちにとってワクチン接種で最も重要なことは、
what do we want most
私たちが一番欲しいものは何ですか
have a memory
記憶がある
have immune memory
免疫記憶がある
That is to say, I have been separated by two years
つまり2年離れてるんですね
three years later
3年後
if the same
同じなら
antigen comes in
抗原が入ってくる
will replace my immune memory
私の免疫記憶を置き換えます
Because many of us are vaccinated
私たちの多くは予防接種を受けているので、
not every few years
数年ごとではない
Same goes for the cold vaccine
風邪のワクチンも同様です
After you hit it, you have to last for a long time
一度打ったら長く続けないといけない
Influenza vaccine every year
インフルエンザワクチンは毎年受けています
If you are vaccinated with sugar
砂糖ワクチンを接種している場合
If you take sugar vaccine
砂糖ワクチンを摂取した場合
your effect
あなたの効果
is relatively short
比較的短いです
because it has less immune memory
免疫記憶が少ないから
Why compare memory without immunity? Because
なぜ免疫なしで記憶を比較するのでしょうか?
The antibodies it produces do not
それが産生する抗体は
Let's say that the cells that produce antibodies are called B cells.
抗体を産生する細胞をB細胞と呼ぶとしましょう。
Antibody-producing cells are not activated by T cells
抗体産生細胞はT細胞によって活性化されない
but if you
しかし、もしあなたが
yes
はい
is useful that
それは便利です
combined vaccine words
ワクチンの単語を組み合わせたもの
It has a longer memory
より長い記憶を持っています
the effect will be longer
効果は長くなります
That's because, as long as you connect it to the egg white
だって、卵の白身とつながっていれば、
it will
そうなる
Destimulate T cells from V cells
V細胞からT細胞の刺激を除去する
T cells come back to activate
T細胞が戻ってきて活性化する
V cells give it memory
V細胞が記憶を与える
I'm not an immunologist myself
私自身は免疫学者ではありません
so i can't make this clear
だからこれをはっきりさせることはできない
But it's the difference
しかし、それは違いです
even
平
If you directly use this polysaccharide
この多糖類を直接使用する場合
Not good for children under two years old
2歳未満の子供には適していません
or older
またはそれ以上の
Sometimes the effect is not good
効果が良くない場合もある
So they have to work hard
だから彼らは一生懸命働かなければならない
make it into a conjugate vaccine
結合型ワクチンにする
This is part of my research
これは私の研究の一部です
you can see
見ることができます
look at this bacteria
この細菌を見てください
This is the bacteria on the cultivated rice
これが培養米についている菌です
One by one for many years
何年もかけて一つ一つ
why is it so sticky
なぜそんなに粘着性があるのですか
because of its shell
その殻のせいで
The outer shell of this bacterium has a strong sugar
この細菌の外殻には強い糖が含まれています
very thick sugar
非常に濃い砂糖
what about this
これはどうですか
we're going to separate it
私たちはそれを分離するつもりです
then made
それから作りました
make that antidote vaccine
その解毒ワクチンを作る
Why is the shell of the bacteria so thick with sugar?
なぜ細菌の殻は砂糖でこんなに分厚いのでしょうか？
Once it enters our body
私たちの体に入ると、
it has that layer of protection
保護層がある
It won't be swallowed by our immune cells
私たちの免疫細胞には飲み込まれない
And what about the layer of sugar?
では砂糖の層はどうでしょうか？
will poison us again
また私たちを毒するだろう
Protecting it can poison us
それを守ると私たちを毒する可能性があります
ok then i
わかりました、それでは私は
about the same time
時間也差不多
i speak faster now
今はもっと早く話せます
our healthy food
私たちの健康食品
The third and last part I will talk about healthy food
最後の3回目は健康食品についてお話します
Dragon Boat Festival is coming
端午節が近づいてきました
Everyone will eat zongzi
みんなでゾンツィを食べるよ
but everyone knows
でも誰もが知っています
Don't eat too much rice dumplings
団子を食べすぎないでください
Because zongzi is difficult to digest
宗子は消化が難しいので
Why Zongzi Are Difficult To Digest
宗子はなぜ消化が難しいのか
We have to look at its structure
その構造を見なければなりません
can you see
見えますか
if we are
私たちがそうであれば
If glutinous rice is used, it will have a lot of nourishment
もち米を使えば栄養もたっぷり
It nourishes a lot, this is glutinous rice
栄養たっぷり、もち米です
This place that is a little bit red is
少し赤いこの場所は
is the non-reducing end, that is, the enzyme
は非還元末端、つまり酵素です
Enzymes can decompose, enzymes can decompose
酵素は分解できる、酵素は分解できる
So it has many places to decompose and can decompose at the same time
そのため、分解する場所が多く、同時に分解する可能性があります。
But if you have less nourishment, probably you only have one or two
しかし、栄養が少ない場合は、おそらく 1 つまたは 2 つしか持っていません。
So in general, it works very quickly at the beginning
したがって、一般に、最初は非常に速く動作します
So glutinous rice is the first, it has a high glycemic index
もち米は最初のものであり、血糖指数が高いです
Because it works very quickly at the beginning, your glycemic index is very fast
最初は非常に早く作用するため、血糖指数が非常に早く上がります。
But, when its enzymes work until
しかし、その酵素が働くまでは、
When reaching this branch point, close to this branch
この分岐点に到達したら、この分岐点に近づく
At the branch point, the enzyme will stop
分岐点で酵素が止まる
Because it can't work anymore, it needs to be replaced with another set
動作しなくなったので、別のセットと交換する必要があります
Enzymes can continue to do
酵素は続けられる
At this moment
この瞬間に
it will, because you can't
それはできる、あなたにはできないから
We humans can't absorb it
私たち人間はそれを吸収することはできません
Therefore, it cannot be decomposed
したがって、分解することはできません
It uses another enzyme to break down
別の酵素を使って分解する
So digestion slows down
そのため消化が遅くなる
Slow down and you will bloat
ゆっくりするとお腹が膨れますよ
Why does it swell?
なぜ膨らむのでしょうか？
Because Syria will use
シリアが使うから
Sometimes talk, because you can't digest
消化できないから時々話す
Digestion is fast at first, but when it arrives
最初は消化が早いですが、到着すると
Indigestion and indigestion later
消化不良とその後の消化不良
So this glutinous rice you have to see
そこでぜひ見ていただきたいのがこのもち米です
its branches, its branches
その枝、その枝
The so-called look at this side, this side is all
いわゆるこっち側を見て、こっち側がすべてです。
Alpha one four connection
アルファワンフォーコネクション
The branch is to become alpha-16 to connect
ブランチは接続するために alpha-16 になります
it has many branches
たくさんの支店があります
Many branches will decompose quickly
多くの枝はすぐに腐ってしまいます
Decomposes slowly
ゆっくりと分解する
Caused by high glycemic index
血糖指数が高いことが原因
I'll let you back
帰らせてもらいます
Poor digestion
消化不良
Because it is slow, so glutinous rice
遅いからもち米
Its indigestibility depends on the structure of its starch
消化しにくさはでんぷんの構造に依存します
it will be clear
それは明らかになるだろう
Some people have diarrhea after drinking milk
牛乳を飲むと下痢をする人もいます。
What about milk diarrhea?
ミルク下痢の場合はどうでしょうか？
Because it's in the milk
牛乳に入っているので
Mostly lactose, this lactose is a disaccharide
大部分は乳糖であり、この乳糖は二糖類です
disaccharide
二糖類
We can't directly absorb and utilize this disaccharide
私たちはこの二糖類を直接吸収して利用することはできません。
This lactose is broken down into
この乳糖が分解されると、
Galactose
ガラクトース
with this glucose
このブドウ糖を使って
have a valid number called lactose hydrolase
乳糖加水分解酵素と呼ばれる有効な番号を持っています
You break it down into a galactose heel
それをガラクトースのかかとに分解すると、
That glucose we can use the simple sugar we can use
そのブドウ糖は私たちが使える単糖を使うことができます
But unfortunately, some people
しかし、残念ながら一部の人は、
no way
とんでもない
or secreted this
あるいはこれを分泌した
lactose hydrolase
乳糖加水分解酵素
very few
非常に少ない
Or, there is no way to decompose it at this time
または、現時点では分解する方法がありません
What about the bacteria hiding inside?
内部に潜む細菌はどうなるのでしょうか？
will come to use
使うようになります
You don't need it, we often go there, there are bacteria in it
必要ありません、私たちはよくそこに行きます、そこには細菌がいます
just take advantage
ただ利用するだけ
The result is often until the bacteria you have been using have been growing a lot
多くの場合、使用しているバクテリアが大量に増殖するまで結果は変わりません。
Then you have diarrhea or gas or something.
その後、下痢やガスなどが発生します。
that's why you milk
だから搾乳するんだよ
Drinking milk will stretch your stomach and make you gas
牛乳を飲むとお腹が張ってガスがたまる
In fact, it has something to do with sugar, your breakdown of sugar.
実際、それは砂糖、つまり砂糖の分解と関係があります。
It does matter, sometimes pigs do too.
それは重要です、時には豚も同様です。
If a pig feeds him this
豚がこれを彼に食べさせたら
this in beans
これは豆で
its sugary
甘いです
material
資料
Pigs can't digest well
豚はうまく消化できない
What about the pigs, the bacteria in the sugar will grow
豚はどうなるか、砂糖の中の細菌が増殖するだろう
will be like us
私たちのようになるでしょう
And what about vitamin C, as we all know
そして、誰もが知っているように、ビタミンCはどうでしょうか？
I eat one almost every day
ほぼ毎日1個食べてます
Then we can't synthesize it, we humans can't synthesize it
それでは合成できません、私たち人間は合成できません。
Most animals can synthesize
ほとんどの動物は合成できる
People I know with this Catholic agency
このカトリック機関の知り合い
Fighting again today
今日も戦います
These two are unable to synthesize vitamin C
この2人はビタミンCを合成できない
Vitamin C in industry
産業におけるビタミンC
it comes directly from glucose
それはブドウ糖から直接得られます
in other plants or animals
他の植物や動物では
They can also be directly converted into vitamin C from glucose
また、ブドウ糖から直接ビタミンCに変換することもできます。
Cut down on vitamin C
ビタミンCを減らす
your gold
あなたの金
Your gold strength must not be strong enough
あなたの金の強さは十分にタフではないはずです
This is industrial glucose
これは工業用ブドウ糖です
Then after two steps it can
2 つのステップを経て、次のことが可能になります。
Vitamin C can be produced
ビタミンCが生成できる
Let's talk about sugar
砂糖について話しましょう
sugar substitute
砂糖代替品
was discovered in England in 1976
1976年にイギリスで発見された
In the United States it was 1998
アメリカでは1998年だった
approved
承認済み
that is, its useful life
つまり耐用年数です
perhaps
多分
20 years
20年
Sugar gold is in 18 years
シュガーゴールドは18年後
only century
たった一世紀
These discoveries of sugar substitutes were made by me by accident.
砂糖代替品のこれらの発見は私によって偶然に行われました。
Then this sugar substitute is called Splendor
この砂糖の代替品はスプレンダーと呼ばれます
Splendor it's made from this sugar
この砂糖から作られる素晴らしさ
The part of the OH with a red dot is all replaced by this green
OH の赤い点でマークされた部分はすべてこの緑色に置き換えられます。
Its sweetness is about 600 times that of sugar
その甘さは砂糖の約600倍！
So, but its advantage is that it is not metabolized in the digestive system
しかし、その利点は、消化器系で代謝されないことです。
can be almost eliminated from the body
ほぼ常に体外に排出される
That is to say, if you don’t know if anyone can substitute sugar for this R48 sweetener
つまり、この R48 甘味料の代わりに砂糖を使用できる人がいるかどうかわからない場合
R48 sweetness is calculated by two calculations
R48の甘さは2つの計算で計算されます
R48 is sweet and this is sweeter than R48 because it is calculated
R48は甘いですが、これは計算されているのでR48より甘いです
If there are amino acids, one of the 20,000 people will have some problems with the metabolism of amino acids
アミノ酸があれば、2万人に1人はアミノ酸の代謝に何らかの問題を抱えている
it produces disease
それは病気を生み出す
Then Aspartia is about 220 times the same as this set
するとアスパルティアはこのセットの約220倍になります
Aspartia also has a bad place, that is
アスパルティアにも悪いところはある
Once it's baked, it's about as sweet as
焼き上がったら、ほんのり甘いです
If it's put in soda, it will also slowly descend
ソーダに入れるとこれもゆっくり下がっていきます
Because soda, if you add carbon dioxide to soda, there will be no carbonation
ソーダに二酸化炭素を加えると炭酸は発生しませんので、
What is the Ph value of carbonated soda?
炭酸ソーダのPh値はどれくらいですか？
4, or lower, how much carbonic acid?
4 以下、炭酸の量はどれくらいですか?
Anyway, it won't be neutral, it should be acidic
とにかく中性ではなく酸性になるはずです
At this time, it is possible for Aspartia to
現時点では、アスパルティアは次のことを行うことができます。
Aspartame may lose its sweetness slowly
アスパルテームは徐々に甘味を失う可能性があります
but this thing it won't
でもこれはそうはならない
Its trade name is Sprander
商品名はスプランダーです
that real name is
その本当の名前は
Sucrose
スクロース
Frankly, I ate this
正直、これ食べました
because it's cheap a kilo
1キロ安いから
Seven or eight thousand Taiwan dollars, made in Canada
7、8千台湾ドル、カナダ製
then you can too
それならあなたもできます
where am i here
私はここどこですか
Where
どこ
foreign
外国
I'm abroad this
これは海外にいます
Summerway saw that they added this
サマーウェイはこれを追加したのを見て
Summerway
サマーウェイ
add this
これを追加
That
それか
good i think
良いと思います
Everyone should be familiar with bird's nest
鳥の巣は誰もが知っているはずです
Because we Orientals, especially Chinese
私たち東洋人、特に中国人だから
think bird's nest is a
鳥の巣だと思います
It's a good nourishment, isn't it?
良い栄養になりますね。
Bird's nest is actually good or bad
ツバメの巣って実は良いのか悪いのか
Decide on two Decide whether it's good or bad There are two
二つに決める 良いか悪いか決める 二つある
One is protein and the other is sugar
1つはタンパク質、もう1つは糖質です
Bird's nest is believed to contain
鳥の巣には次のものがあると考えられています
sugar
糖
High amount of dehydrating acid
多量の脱水酸
His good or bad dehydrating acid if the content is high
含有量が多い場合、彼の良いまたは悪い脱水酸
they think it's good
彼らはそれが良いと思っている
I'm sorry because I don't know
分からないのでごめんなさい
what if i ate it
食べたらどうなるの？
Does it have nutritional or health benefits?
栄養や健康上の利点はありますか?
I do not know about this
これについてはわかりません
I'm going to ask that nutritionist
その栄養士さんに聞いてみます
okay i say good things
わかりました、良いことを言います
That leaf environmentalist is here to scold me
あの葉っぱの環境活動家が私を叱りに来た
I'm sorry because I really don't know
本当に分からないのでごめんなさい
Is it good or bad to eat bird's nest?
ツバメの巣を食べるのは良いのか悪いのか？
Then bring it down
それからそれを降ろしてください
This is my real experiment
これが私の本当の実験です
I did the last two years
ここ2年はやったよ
That is to say, everyone will say
つまり、誰もが言うでしょう
edible mushroom polysaccharide
食用キノコ多糖類
I really polysaccharides in my experiment
実験では本当に多糖類ができました
It's mushrooms
キノコです
two kinds of mushrooms
2種類のキノコ
One is dirty beef juice
一つは汚い牛肉汁
one is black fungus
一つは黒菌です
he really
彼は本当に
we confirm
私たちは確認します
He can really enhance people's immunity
彼は人々の免疫力を本当に高めることができます
It activates giant cells
巨大細胞を活性化します
These giant cells are our immune cells
この巨大細胞は私たちの免疫細胞です
It can increase the bactericidal phagocytosis of giant cells
巨細胞の殺菌性食作用を増加させることができます
can also increase the strength of a person who inhales endotoxins
エンドトキシンを吸入した人の体力も増加する可能性があります
If we say that when we get infected in the hospital
病院で感染したときにそんなことを言ったら
If we usually eat more of these mushrooms
私たちが普段これらのキノコをもっと食べると
It is possible to suffer from the septicemia just now
今すぐ敗血症になる可能性があります
It will be lessened, maybe
軽減されるかも知れません
this of course it is we are
これはもちろん私たちです
The polysaccharide structure of this beef dirty juice
この牛汚汁の多糖類構造
analyze it and see how it looks
それを分析してどのように見えるかを確認します
This part of the reaction is doing Yilan University
反応のこの部分は宜蘭大学が行っています
Professor Hua helped us do it
ホア教授がそれを手伝ってくれました
Well, some people also say that this is the starting value of chitin
まあ、これがキチンの初期値だという人もいます
These are polysaccharides
これらは多糖類です
Then sometimes this can be used in agriculture
そうすると場合によっては農業にも使えます
Can enhance plant health or
植物の健康を強化したり、
Resistance
抵抗
Some people also say that you eat alphanuclides
アルファ核種を食べているという人もいます
Can lose weight and lower cholesterol
体重を減らし、コレステロールを下げることができます
because
なぜなら
There are some alphanuclides it is put this
これにアルファ核種がいくつかあります
by
に
to suck
吸う
After this cut it off
このあと切りました
it is belt
それはベルトです
It is also positively charged
プラスにも帯電している
can put some
いくつか置くことができます
What about charged fatty acids?
荷電した脂肪酸はどうでしょうか？
take it
それを取る
Adsorb and then
吸着してから
take it out of the body
体から取り出す
Some people say it can lose weight
痩せるという人もいる
I don't know
わからない
But there are many healthy foods
でも健康食品もたくさんあるよ
squeeze nails
爪を絞る
Squeeze the nail is the top
爪を絞るのが上です
Then a nuclide
それから核種
just leave it at this
このままにしておいてください
this
これ
this removes it
これで削除されます
just let it electrify
ただ感電させてください
What about this one? I encourage you a little.
これはどうでしょうか?少しお勧めします。
this is the same
これも同じです
This micro-encouragement is the same
この小さな励ましも同じです
Grape Chang'an
グレープ長安
It is mainly a cartilage mechanism
主に軟骨の仕組みです
like our joints
私たちの関節のように
Osteoarthritis as we age
加齢に伴う変形性関節症
Osteoarthritis is primarily
変形性関節症は主に、
Why do our joints have cartilage?
なぜ私たちの関節には軟骨があるのでしょうか?
because it is mainly cartilage-forming
主に軟骨を形成するため
Cartilage absorbs a lot of water
軟骨は水分を多く吸収します
increase the awareness of this joint
この関節の意識を高める
So Glucose
それでグルコース
It can provide you with this recognition
この認識を提供できます
Can also do this hyaluronic acid is also a glucose
こんなこともできる ヒアルロン酸もブドウ糖です
It can also be a type of hyaluronic acid
ヒアルロン酸の一種でもあります
like hyaluronic acid
像波尿酸
it's more useful
それはもっと便利です
Whether it is cosmetic moisturizing
化粧品の保湿なのか
The current ones can be mass-produced with follow-up
現状のものはフォローアップで量産可能です
what was the earliest
一番早かったのは何ですか
Take it out from the organ, the attacking organ
臓器、攻撃臓器から取り出す
What is the use of
用途は何ですか
If you go to some places like Hong Kong, there is Saima
香港などに行くとサイマがあります
Saima's horse
サイマの馬
it joint this this
それはこれを結合します
Saima joints are treated with cloth uric acid
Saima 関節は布尿酸で処理されています
I don't know if the real Saima is playing in the early days or not
本物のサイマが初期にプレイしているかどうかはわかりません
I used to watch when I was a kid and I couldn't understand
子供の頃よく見てたけど理解できなかった
But that's all he uses
でも彼が使うのはそれだけだ
Well, I think this molecule has a lot of cousins.
そうですね、この分子にはたくさんのいとこがあると思います。
In fact, it's related to both cancer and the immune system.
実際、それはがんと免疫系の両方に関係しています。
In fact
実際には
In front of Vice President Liu, I'm playing tricks
劉副大統領の前でイタズラしてる
In fact, er, Vice President Liu is also an expert of Tangzi.
実は、あの、劉副総統は塘子の専門家でもあります。
Especially in this galactose
特にこのガラクトースでは
Galactose
半乳糖的
Galactose Lingjisu 3
半乳糖凌吉素3
It's our Vice President Liu
私たちの副社長リューです
found
見つかった
Is it related to cancer?
癌と関係があるのでしょうか？
If you are on this side
あなたがこちら側にいるなら
of course to ask
もちろん尋ねるために
Vice President Liu, I, I, really
劉副大統領、私、本当に
So when I talk about this, I probably want to say something
だから、このことについて話すとき、おそらく何か言いたいことがあります
But at the end I want to introduce Tangzi Science Education Foundation to you
最後に、Tangzi Science Education Foundation を紹介したいと思います。
Minister Liu just said that the police mourned the professor and his wife
劉大臣は、警察は教授とその妻を悼んだと述べたばかりである。
to Taiwan in 1996
1996年に台湾へ
Because at that time the University of Tokyo was a national university in Japan
なぜなら当時、東京大学は日本の国立大学でした。
It is about 60 years old and must retire
年齢は約60歳なので引退しなければなりません
So he in 1994
それで彼は1994年に
Why does he have so much affection for Taiwan?
なぜ彼はこれほどまでに台湾に愛情を注ぐのでしょうか？
because he is born
彼は生まれたから
he was born in taiwan
彼は台湾で生まれました
Then he didn't return to Japan until he was 11 or 12 years old
それから彼は11歳か12歳になるまで日本に戻りませんでした。
So he returned to Japan in 1945 or 1946
そこで彼は1945年か1946年に日本に帰国しました。
So he is willing to come to Taiwan
それで彼は台湾に行きたいと思っています
And in Taiwan
そして台湾では
and his wife's salary are all built
彼の妻の給料はすべて自分で稼いだものです
Establish the Tangzi Foundation
唐子財団を設立
At that time, of course, Dean Li was established in 2002
当時はもちろんディーン・リーが設立された2002年
Dean Li also went to raise funds
ディーン・リーも募金活動に行った
There are several like Uniform Yimei
ユニフォームイーメイのようなものはいくつかあります
and gold car
そしてゴールドカー
And Yong Fengyu's family
そして永峰裕さんのご家族
Under the call of Dean Li
ディーン・リーの呼びかけで
Also set up a foundation
基礎も整える
But in 2003
しかし2003年に
Former Dean Weng returned to Taiwan
ウェン前学部長が台湾に帰国
Foundation Center
財団センター
His power is much greater than the foundation
彼の力は基礎よりもはるかに大きい
Over the past 10 years, our foundation
過去10年間にわたり、私たちの基盤は
didn't play very well
あまり上手にプレーできませんでした
Because Dean Weng has taken the lead in
ディーン・ウェンが主導権を握っているので、
make a lot of pushes in this direction
この方向にたくさんプッシュする
In the future, I hope that everyone
将来的には、皆さんが
Learn about our foundation
私たちの財団について学ぶ
In fact our slogan is
実際、私たちのスローガンは
Kangzhi Technology Anti-disease and anti-aging
Kangzhi Technology 抗疾患と抗老化
This is our logo
これが私たちのロゴです
ok thank you all
わかりました、皆さんありがとう
Thanks
ありがとう
Well, thanks to Dr. Wu Zhixiong for being very informative
非常に有益な情報を提供してくれた Wu Zhixiong 博士に感謝します
and a very careful speech
そしてとても丁寧なスピーチでした
So now open up some of that questioning
それでは、その疑問の一部を明らかにしてください
I also encourage you to ask
ぜひ聞いてみることをお勧めします
So if we ask
それで私たちが尋ねると
would give a very nice one
とてもいいものをくれるだろう
Is it a cup type cup electricity?
カップ型のカップ電でしょうか？
ok over here
はい、こちらです
Why is the non-reducing side crowded out of here
なぜ非還元側がここから混雑しているのですか
can say it again
もう一度言えます
This is a basic structure of Tang Zi
これが『唐子の』基本構造です
he must
他一定
almost always use one to pick up
ほとんどの場合、ピックアップに 1 つを使用します
he can pick up at six
彼は6時に迎えに行ける
can be picked up in four
4つで拾える
can be connected in three
3つに接続できます
can be connected in two
2つに接続できます
As long as there is OH, he can pick it up
OHがある限り拾ってくれる
Tropical acid exception
托一酸例外
Tropical acid is connected with two
トロピカルアシッドは2つでつながります
But his structure is
しかし彼の構造は
just the same
全く同じで
that is
あれは
Take it like this, after you take it
撮ったらこうやって撮って
The non-reducing end must be the outermost
非還元端は最も外側でなければなりません
because he was connected
彼は繋がっていたから
He combines with fat or with
彼は脂肪と組み合わせたり、
protein binding is to use his
タンパク質の結合は彼のものを利用することです
restore terminal
端末を復元する
That one, didn’t you mention H and N just now?
あれ、さっきHとNのことを言いませんでしたか？
Isn't that N used to cut that H?
あのHをカットするのにNが使ったんじゃないの？
N is cutting acid
Nは酸を切断します
cut acid
酸をカットする
Because it is deacidified, hydrolyzed
脱酸、加水分解されているため、
N
N
So if you see H1N1
したがって、H1N1 に遭遇した場合は、
this is him
これが彼です
He has many categories, like H generally has 16 categories
H には通常 16 のカテゴリがあるように、彼には多くのカテゴリがあります。
N has 9 categories
Nには9つのカテゴリがあります
this is normal
これは正常です
Then how to divide it, yes
じゃあどうやって分けるか、はい
it's this virus that got to us
このウイルスが私たちに侵入したのです
Antibodies produced by the body
体内で産生される抗体
Sometimes these antibodies are used to classify
場合によっては、これらの抗体は分類に使用されます。
The N will only work after he has to leave
N は、彼が去らなければならない後にのみ機能します
or before infection he will
あるいは感染する前に彼はそうするだろう
this is a good question
これは良い質問です
Its virus is a very good distribution of H and N
そのウイルスは、H と N が非常によく分布しています。
H is about 3 to 4 times N
HはNの3～4倍程度
About 3 to 4 times outside
屋外で3～4回程度
If I hadn't been very careful just now
もし今私が十分に注意していなかったら
I said its amount is the amount on the surface of the virus
その量はウイルスの表面の量だと言いました
H will be more than N
HはNより大きくなります
about 3 to 4 times more
3～4倍くらい
So when it is picked up, N must play first
したがって、それを拾ったら、N が最初にプレイする必要があります
I said N it's going to find dehydrating acid
私は言った、脱水酸を見つけるつもりだ
The dehydrating acid must be found at the outermost end
脱水酸は最外端に存在する必要があります
then this is the first step
それならこれが最初のステップです
It is the first step to enter the cell
それは細胞に入る第一歩です
I think I still want to ask about vaccines.
ワクチンについても引き続きお聞きしたいと思います。
What does 13 plus 23 plus mean?
13プラス23プラスってどういう意味ですか？
That is to say, if you go to see dried mushrooms in Tai Tam
つまり、タイタムに干しキノコを見に行くなら
I use Tai Tam dried fungus and everyone will know better
私はタイタム乾燥菌を使っていますが、皆さんもよくご存知でしょう。
a bacteria
一種序菌
its
これは
Sugar out there is ever-changing
世の中の砂糖は常に変化しています
ever-changing
常に変化する
If you say big sugar dry
大砂糖ドライと言ったら
How many kinds does it have
何種類あるのかな
Types of sugar outside
外の砂糖の種類
Hundreds of
何百もの
Hundreds of each
それぞれ数百個
we just look at
私たちはただ見ているだけです
What kind of
どんな
That is to say, initially there were 7
つまり、最初は7つだったということです。
these 7
この7つ
These 7 kinds
この7種類
Streptococcus pneumoniae
肺炎連鎖球菌
nosocomial infection
院内感染
Play these 7 kinds first
まずはこの7種類をプレイしてみよう
In the future you will put these 7 kinds
今後はこの7種類を使用します
After crushing it?
潰した後は？
anything else
他に何か
other species will
他の種は
in charge
担当
So add 13 more
さらに 13 個追加します
plus 23 kinds
プラス23種類
so
それで
These vaccines are not absolute, you still follow
これらのワクチンは絶対ではありませんが、それでも従う必要があります
False progress is racing
間違った進歩が競い合っている
It's a good thing the research is endless, or I'd be out of a job.
研究に終わりがないのは良いことだが、そうでなければ私は仕事を失ってしまうだろう。
right
右
What this research can't do is to fight like this
この研究でできないことは、このように戦うことです
by bwd6
by bwd6
good
良い
Teacher Wu has two questions about Niu Zhang Chi
ウー先生が牛張池について 2 つの質問があります。
The first question is that the octopus fungus grows on ordinary wood
最初の疑問は、タコ菌は普通の木材にも生えるということです。
What's the difference between growing on the ox octopus
牛タコで育てるのと何が違うの？
The second problem is its toxicity to Niu Zhang Chi
2番目の問題は、牛張池に対する毒性です。
Is it to the extent that it will hurt people?
人を傷つけるほどですか？
Because I'm not a fanatic
私はマニアではないので、
so sorry it's hard for me to answer your question
申し訳ありませんが、あなたの質問に答えるのは難しいです
When I have retired colleagues who do just that
退職した同僚が同じようなことをしているとき
he knows better than me
彼は私よりもよく知っています
I may answer wrong here
ここで間違った答えをするかもしれません
because i don't know much
私はあまり知らないので
I'm crazy about being a cow
私は牛になることに夢中です
People have done a lot
人々はたくさんのことをしてきた
I just came in to do it
それをするために来ただけだ
But what I do is limit in Duotang
でも、私がやることはDuotangでは限界があります
There are many others like tri-iron
トライアイアンなど他にもたくさんあります
A bunch of them, what are you doing?
彼らの束、何をしているのですか？
Well, to be honest, I don't understand enough.
うーん、正直に言うと、よくわかりません。
Sorry I can't answer your question
ごめんなさい、あなたの質問に答えることができません
ok ask again
わかりました、もう一度聞いてください
thanks ok i have a question is it ok to have a punch
ありがとう、分かった、質問があるんだけどパンチしてもいいですか？
One question is about experts H1N1
質問の 1 つは、専門家の H1N1 についてです。
So do these numbers have any special significance?
では、これらの数字には特別な意味があるのでしょうか?
What is the N level? Does the N level have any special meaning?
N レベルとは何ですか? N レベルには特別な意味がありますか?
Thanks
ありがとう
is there any special meaning
何か特別な意味があるのですか
what does that mean
どういう意味ですか
I don't know about N1 and N2
N1とN2は分かりません
because that is in fact
それが実際にあるから
The difference in the sequence of amino acid caused his this
アミノ酸配列の違いが彼の症状を引き起こした
Antibodies produced by blood type will be different
血液型によって作られる抗体が異なる
sorry i don't know
ごめんなさい、わかりません
Now that means in 1918 it was N1 H1
つまり、1918 年には N1 H1 だったということになります。
There was also a pandemic in 1957
1957年にもパンデミックがありました
it is N2 H2
それはN2H2です
There was also a pandemic in 1968
1968年にもパンデミックがありました
That one I remember is H2 H3 N2
私が覚えているのは H2 H3 N2 です
then what
じゃあ何
Then in the end it is 1 2 3 in the end
そうすると結局は 1 2 3 です
I think it's a category
カテゴリーだと思います
it's not different
それは違いません
Its Ankywan sequence is not the same cause
そのアンキワンの秩序は同じ原因ではありません
because it's protein
プロテインなので
So it is possible that H1 N1 will come back
つまり、H1 N1が戻ってくる可能性があります
possible
可能
still never come back
まだ戻ってこない
Probably will come back
おそらく戻ってくるでしょう
I can not do it
私はそれを行うことはできません
will look back
振り返るだろう
That is H1 N1 is just in H1 N1
つまり、H1 N1 はちょうど H1 N1 の中にあります。
likely to reappear
再発する可能性が高い
show up again
再び現れる
another comment
別のコメント
About Lushan
廬山について
I'm sorry, I'm Lu Shan
ごめんなさい、私はルーシャンです
yes
はい
perch acid
パーチ酸
Exercising only when you are tired
疲れたときにだけ運動する
Perch acid can only be produced under anaerobic metabolism
パーチ酸は嫌気性代謝下でのみ生成されます
the research we did
私たちが行った研究
we use
を使用しております
We do sports nutrition research
私たちはスポーツ栄養の研究を行っています
Then we do exhaustion exercise
それから消耗運動をします
Wale Train athletes
Wale Train的運動員
It's the mountain iron player
山鉄プレイヤーです
his fatigue
彼の疲労
to perch acid to achieve a bath of high quality
パーチ酸で高品質な浴を実現
it's dying
それは死にかけています
Its very high concentration of perch acid
非常に高濃度のパーチ酸
It clears up in about 15 to 20 minutes
15～20分くらいで消えます
stop and clear
停止してクリアする
won't wait until the next day
次の日まで待てません
So fast
非常に高速
so it this
それでこれです
its perch
その止まり木
so tired the next day
次の日はとても疲れた
It's not because of perch
止まり木のせいじゃないよ
It's because of the action of delayed onset muscle acid
それは遅発性筋酸の作用によるものです
delayed muscle soreness
遅発性筋肉痛
because of a muscle injury
筋肉の損傷のため
So it has nothing to do with perch
だからヒナとは関係ないよ
so no reference
だから参考にならない
Thanks
ありがとう
here
ここ
Hello Professor Wu
こんにちは、ウー教授
My problem is just that
私の問題はそれだけです
The controgated vaccine of Numococcus
Numococcus の対照ワクチン
he
他
I'm curious about his carrier
彼のキャリアに興味がある
what will it be
それは何でしょう
and hit us inside
そして私たちを中に殴り込みます
because we also develop some antibodies to it
私たちもそれに対する抗体を生成するからです
what kind of thing is it
それはどんなものですか
We feel it's a safe way to use this
これを使用するのが安全な方法だと考えています
This is because of the carrier protein
これはキャリアタンパク質のせいです
fixed
修理済み
like rhinotoxin
鼻毒素のような
after it detoxifies
解毒した後
many people are using
多くの人が使っています
becomes a carrier protein
キャリアタンパク質になる
even you can buy
あなたでも買えます
then why use this
ではなぜこれを使うのか
This detoxified white monkey is toxic
この解毒された白猿は有毒です
I'm thinking that someone missed the research
誰かが研究を見逃したのではないかと思う
Well, I don't have a big problem with this aspect.
まあ、この点に関しては大きな問題はありません。
Research
研究
So it is the detoxification of the white monkey
つまり白猿の解毒です
That
それか
One of these is a white monkey
そのうちの一匹は白い猿です
Then the carrier vaccine we used
次に、私たちが使用したキャリアワクチン
will it be
そうなるだろうか
Although the white monkey is almost out of muscle
白猿はもう筋肉が尽きかけていますが、
But do we also develop antibodies against it?
しかし、私たちはそれに対する抗体も開発するのでしょうか？
a bit curious
少し好奇心旺盛
of course
もちろん
Because it's still a foreign antigen?
まだ外来抗原だから？
I'm addressing the question asked by the lady just in front of me
目の前の女性の質問に答えています
I remember that H
Hさんのことを思い出しました
It is Hema Glutinin
ヘマグルチニンです
Is it related to Host specificity?
ホストの特異性に関係していますか?
H123 seems to be the key to open the Human Flu
H123はヒトインフルエンザを開く鍵のようです
And that H57 is the key to Avian Flu
そして、H57が鳥インフルエンザの鍵であるということ
We'll simply say
単純に言います
Yes, but many people at the scene should know
はい、でも現場にいる多くの人は知っているはずです
So I play big swords in front of sightseeing
だから観光の前で大剣をするんだ
ok thank you sir
わかりました、ありがとうございます
yes
はい
The one I want to ask is just about Cerule protein
セルールプロテインについて聞きたいのですが
The teacher said that Cerule protein can last longer
先生はセルールプロテインの方が長持ちすると言っていました
Because it can start the memory of the Tc package
Tcパッケージのメモリを起動できるため
Then everyone will explain in detail
そしたらみんなが詳しく説明してくれるよ
Because I don't know much about the intermediate process
途中の工程がよくわからないので
I don't think I'm an immunologist
私は免疫学者ではないと思います
to help you explain this
これを説明するのに役立つように
I'm afraid I can't explain it clearly.
はっきりと説明できないと思いますが、
but this is
しかし、これは
If we put it into this
これに入れてみると
at this place
この場所で
If it is a multiple hall
複合ホールの場合
It can't be B
Bではありえない
It has no way to Present is
プレゼントする方法はありません
MHC2 here
MHC2はこちら
It has no way to generate this to follow B
B に続くようにこれを生成する方法はありません
Come talk to T
Tさんに相談しに来てください
If you only have multiple halls
ホールが複数ある場合
If you are Duotang
ドゥオタンなら
If you are a carbohydrate antigen
炭水化物抗原の場合
attached to protein
タンパク質に付​​着している
Connected to this Protonite
このプロトナイトとつながっています
it can
できる
After B can talk to T
B が T と会話できるようになったら
T cells in
T細胞
secrete some
ある程度分泌する
in the looking what is this Chinese
見てみると、この中国語は何ですか
Boundary number
境界番号
and then stimulate this
そしてこれを刺激します
So the main difference is whether he can perform
つまり、主な違いは彼がパフォーマンスを発揮できるかどうかだ
It is the expression of this antigen that causes him to be
この抗原の発現により、彼は
difference in the effect of memory
記憶の効果の違い
i know now
私は今知っています
But I just said I'm not an immunologist
でも私は免疫学者ではないと言いました
Maybe there are immunologists here
もしかしたらここに免疫学者がいるかもしれない
can help me answer
答えられるようにしてください
Then I'll go find it myself
じゃあ自分で探しに行くよ
Thank you, teacher
ありがとう、先生
High school textbooks say that the B cell
高校の教科書にはB細胞と書いてあります。
If it is a polysaccharide antigen
多糖類抗原の場合
B cell is to do the receptor mediated endocytosis
B細胞は受容体媒介エンドサイトーシスを行う
Then activate to become that plasma cell
次に、その形質細胞になるように活性化します
But then it can't use that mc
しかし、そうするとそのMCは使えなくなります
to present antigen
抗原を提示する
去activate specific dehelper
特定のヘルパー解除を解除する
so it doesn't have that
だからそれはありません
it still produces specific antibodies
それでも特異的な抗体を産生する
there is no merry
陽気がない
But the main thing is to understand why
しかし、重要なことはその理由を理解することです
If you add QQ protein to QQ protein
QQプロテインにQQプロテインを加えると
It can be started but if it is not added
起動はできるが追加されていない場合
It is more difficult to express
表現するのはもっと難しいです
thank you thank you teacher
ありがとう、ありがとう先生
here for sir
先生のためにここに
Mr. Wu would like to ask you for advice
ウーさんからアドバイスをいただきたいのですが
Just now you talked about that EPO
先ほど EPO について話しましたね
Can we talk a little more about the kidneys?
腎臓についてもう少し話してもいいですか？
For example, the one
たとえば、
Kidney dialysis patients will have flat blood
腎臓透析患者は血液が平らになります
About the relationship between EPO and the kidney
EPOと腎臓の関係について
Teacher, can you talk a little more?
先生、もう少し話してもらえますか？
like erythrocyte renin
赤血球レニンのような
because
なぜなら
Kidney dialysis man
腎臓透析の男性
This one from EPO
これはEPOのものです
Erythrocyte renin will be less
赤血球レニンが減少します
because he is the most important
彼が一番大事だから
Epo is secreted from our kidney cells
Epoは腎臓細胞から分泌されます
Then the kidney cells of your kidney dialysis person will be
そうすれば、腎臓透析を受けている人の腎臓細胞は次のようになります。
will be weaker
弱くなるだろう
he can't have
彼にはそれができない
Appropriate amount out
適量出ます
then if you have
もしあなたが持っているなら
If the doctor gives you an injection
医師が注射をした場合
Your red blood cell count will increase
赤血球数が増加します
Then your normal blood will be relieved
そうすれば正常な血液が楽になります
you will be more energetic
あなたはもっと元気になるでしょう
Because after all, red blood cells are
なぜなら、結局のところ、赤血球は
Oxygen?
空気？
We know oxygen consumption
酸素消費量はわかっています
It has a lot to do with our energy
それは私たちのエネルギーと大きく関係しています
ask a question
質問する
That is to say, it is mentioned that it is cow's dirty juice
つまり牛の汚汁であると記載されています
And that black fungus
そしてあの黒い菌は
Its polysaccharides are activated
多糖類が活性化される
The function of that megalithic cell
その巨石細胞の働き
then i want to ask
それから聞きたいです
I don't know if it has been compared
比較されたかどうかは分かりませんが、
The two sources of polysaccharides
これら 2 つの供給源からの多糖類
Does it work differently
動作が異なりますか
and because we know
そして私たちは知っているので
Does beef offal seem expensive?
牛もつは高そうに見えますか？
Then I asked if I should actually eat more black fungus
それから私は実際にもっと黒菌を食べるべきかどうか尋ねました
it's ok
それでおしまい
Thanks
ありがとう
can you help me answer this question
この質問に答えるのを手伝ってもらえますか
In fact, other effective
実は牛編が効果的
People have always believed that the effective ingredients are not only multitasking
人々は常に、効果的な成分はマルチタスクであるだけではないと信じてきました。
But because I want to be different from other people who study
でも勉強する他の人とは違うことをしたいから
Because people are making too many other active ingredients
人々が他の有効成分を作りすぎているため
The person who studied Niu Zhangzhi has been in Taiwan for a long time
牛章志を研究した人は台湾に長く住んでいます
But I haven't seen anyone who does multiple halls come out.
でも複数のホールをやっている人は見たことがありません。
The reason is that it is definitely not that simple for you to understand the structure of Duotang
その理由は、Duotang の構造を理解するのは決して簡単ではないからです。
That's why we thought we'd try and see what we put in to do this
だからこそ私たちは、これを行うために何を注ぐかを試してみようと考えたのです
I want to differentiate myself from other researchers
他の研究者との差別化を図りたい
If you separate, you are more effective
分離したほうが効果的です
Opportunity to receive research funding from the Ministry of Science and Technology
科学技術省から研究資金を受け取る機会
different from everyone
みんなとは違う
I use this idea to do this research
私はこのアイデアを使ってこの研究を行っています
In fact, the research time is quite long.
実際、研究期間はかなり長いです。
It will probably take three or four years
おそらく3～4年はかかるだろう
A doctoral student wants to
博士課程の学生がやりたいこと
Those two things take four years in a doctoral program
この2つは博士課程で4年かかります
to finish it
それを終わらせるために
there is a gentleman behind
後ろに紳士がいます
sorry, i want to ask
すみません、聞きたいのですが
can explain a little bit
少し説明できます
When we study sugar
砂糖を勉強するとき
The process of storage and separation
保管と分別のプロセス
Because sugars are not like amino acids in proteins
糖はタンパク質のアミノ酸とは異なるため、
there is only one solution
解決策は1つだけです
it can have many solutions
多くの解決策が考えられます
And there are not only twenty types of sugar
砂糖の種類は20種類だけではありません
So you can ask me a little bit
それで少し聞いてもいいですか
how to actually do
実際にどうするか
How to do
実行する方法
It is the method of storing and identifying
保存・識別する方法です。
is to recognize the difference
違いを認識することです
generally like sugar
一般的に砂糖が好き
Sugar research is slow to find
砂糖の研究は発見が遅い
but progress is slow
しかし進歩は遅い
But recently progress is faster
しかし最近の進歩は比較的早い
Progress is slow for two reasons
進歩が遅い理由は 2 つあります
Because your chemistry didn't keep up
あなたの化学反応が追いつかなかったから
like this
このような
For protein
プロテイン用
Its synthesis can be automated
合成は自動化できます
After the 80s
80年代以降
genetic function
遺伝機能
to produce the protein of our medicine
私たちの薬のタンパク質を生産するため
that for this DNA
それはこの DNA の場合
or RNA speaking
またはRNAの話
Also because of the synthetic technique
それも合成技術のせいで
and we say
そして私たちは言います
How do you say PCR is a table in Chinese?
PCRは中国語で表と言いますか？
right
右
ex girl
前女生
After these developments
こうした展開の後、
So DNA
つまりDNA
The research on this nucleic acid should be done as much as possible
この核酸に関する研究は可能な限り行われるべきである
So sugar is the first one you can detect, you can’t detect it
砂糖は最初に検出できるものですが、検出することはできません
because we're detecting proteins and nucleic acids
タンパク質と核酸を検出しているため
We can use ultraviolet light
紫外線を利用できる
But with sugar you can't detect it in ultraviolet light
でも砂糖の場合は紫外線では検出できない
Therefore, it is an obstacle to both analysis and synthesis.
したがって、これは分析と合成の両方にとって障害となります。
That is the way you said just now.
それが今あなたがおっしゃったやり方です。
You probably only have at most two ways of connecting two amino acids.
おそらく、2 つのアミノ酸を結合する方法は多くても 2 つしかありません。
One N segment and one C segment at most two
N セグメント 1 つと C セグメント 1 つ、最大 2 つ
Go see if one amino acid becomes two amino acids
1つのアミノ酸が2つのアミノ酸になるかどうかを確認してください
In terms of diamine, it is a kind of
ジアミンに関して言えば、
But sugar, a monosaccharide linked to a disaccharide
しかし、砂糖は二糖類に結合した単糖類です
it has eleven types so its complexity is high
11種類あるので複雑度が高い
And it's a lot more indirect like Avaboda Iii Izo
そしてそれはAvaboda Iii Izoのようなもっと間接的なものです
It's complicated, but it's really inside a living organism
複雑ですが、実際は生物の内部です
not that complicated
そんなに複雑ではない
why
なぜ
Because he wants to pick up a Tang sword
唐の剣を手に取りたいから
He's wasting a gene
彼は遺伝子を無駄にしている
pick him up to make one
彼を迎えに来て作ってもらう
synthesized like you
あなたのように合成された
At once
すぐに
Alpha medical affairs
アルファ医療事務
or Beta Medicine
またはベータ医学
is to consume a gene
遺伝子を消費することです
is a valid number
有効な数値です
to lead this
これを導くために
people
人
Genes are coded
遺伝子はコード化されている
forming Tang sword
唐の剣を形成する
about 200
約200
various efficacies
さまざまな効能
we call this
私たちはこれをそう呼んでいます
Glycoxial Transverse
グリコキシアルトランスバース
how to translate
翻訳方法
That's about 200 or so
それって200くらいかな
so
それで
you can watch
あなたは見ることができます
his true presence
彼の本当の存在
The structure is not so complicated
構造はそれほど複雑ではありません
I think
私が思うに
The hard part is
難しい部分は、
Modifications on the Tang Sword
唐刀の改造
this is difficult
これは難しいです
A single hyaluronic acid
単一のヒアルロン酸
he was groomed probably
彼はおそらく手入れされていた
there is
がある
Forty or fifty ways of repairing
40～50通りの修復方法
this is hard
これはきつい
If you just modify it
ただ改造するだけなら
Its combination with the number of coagulation poles changes the
凝固極の数との組み合わせにより、
any modification
任意の変更
So the difficulty is here
問題はここにあります
I think it's very difficult because
とても難しいと思うので、
As for the real Tang Jian?
本物の唐建は？
sometimes if you have
時々あなたが持っているなら
You can also send it to help others.
他の人を助けるために送信することもできます。
1,500 yuan broke two days without gold
1,500元は金なしの2日間で壊れた
They did it for you
彼らはあなたのためにそれをしてくれました
Do you have any other questions
他にご質問はありますか
Just now it seems that there is someone thinking about Fangwen in the back
今、奥でファンウェンのことを考えている人がいるみたいだ
Wait a moment
等一下
I just talked about the Dotang vaccine
先ほどドータンワクチンについてお話しました。
For the elderly and children under the age of two
お年寄りと2歳以下のお子様向け
Effect
効果
Why is his effect on these two ethnic groups less effective?
なぜ彼はこれら 2 つの民族グループに対してあまり効果的ではないのでしょうか?
Then there is his so-called short effect
それから彼のいわゆるショート効果があります
If the effect is short, how short is it?
効果が短い場合、どれくらい短いですか?
Then for such an application on the pre-hospital study
次に、入院前の研究に関するそのようなアプリケーションについては、
What kind of applicable timing?
どのようなタイミングが該当しますか？
that is
あれは
this is really sorry
本当にごめんなさい
because I
なぜなら私は
first i am not a doctor
まず、私は医者ではありません
The dean of liufu is actually a doctor
六福大学の学部長は実は医者です
It seems to say that only polysaccharides are used instead of that
その代わりに多糖類だけを使っていると言うそうです。
You can do it without Count
カウントなしでもできます
no carrier
キャリアなし
is it not good
良くないですか
still the same as before
まだ前と同じ
The carrier is to increase his immunity
キャリアは免疫力を高める必要があります
Will cause T-cell Response
T細胞反応を引き起こす
Then T-cell is T helper
T細胞はTヘルパーです
It is Hel B-cell
それはヘルB細胞です
This kind of concept about this kind
このようなコンセプト
Simply put it like this
簡単に言うとこのようになります
Then at this stage
それではこの段階で
Because just now we talked about 23 and 13
だってさっき23と13の話をしたから
Since these two are polysaccharide vaccines and conjugate vaccines, there is a difference
この2つは多糖体ワクチンと結合型ワクチンなので違いがあります
Then there are products on his food now?
では、今彼の食べ物に製品はありますか？
for is
というのは
Is it really a polysaccharide vaccine?
それは本当に多糖体ワクチンですか？
is there such a
そんなものはありますか
you say
あなたは言う
It should be NUEMO COCKER
ヌエモコッカーのはず
Vaccine is polysaccharide
ワクチンは多糖類です
13 is
13は
come to get a vaccine
ワクチンをもらいに来てください
is a conjugate vaccine
結合型ワクチンです
Yeah, he just talked about a 23 frame being polysaccharide
ええ、彼は 23 フレームが多糖類であることについて話しました。
right
右
23 is the same
23も同じだよ
is also a carrier
運送業者でもあります
Is it also a carrier?
それも運送業者ですか？
yes yes no
はい、はい、いいえ
No information I see is
私が見た情報はありません
yes he is more than one
はい、彼は複数です
a polisacra
一個polisacra
what's his name
彼のお名前は
You have a vaccine Samyam
サムヤムはワクチンを持っています
Yeah
うん
I
私
no no no this
いやいやこれは
he is this
彼はこれです
PPV?
PPV？
He's PPV so a polisacra vaccine
彼はPPVだからポリサクラワクチン
Is this information wrong? I don't know
この情報は間違っていますか?わかりません
The mayor mayor can already have 23
市長はすでに23人を持つことができます
There are 23
23個あります
The range of protection is about 80%
防御範囲は約80%
8 Narita
8成多
Because it's short-acting but I don't know how short-acting it is
短時間作用型だからだけど、どのくらい短時間作用型なのかは分からない
this may be
これはそうかもしれない
Short-acting sometimes varies from person to person
短時間作用性は人によって異なる場合があります
I don't know, I really don't know
分からない、本当に分からない
good committee
グッドシェンウェイ
our last question
私たちの最後の質問
I remember we commemorate the pneumonia vaccine
肺炎ワクチンを記念したことを覚えています
It means that you only need to play once in a lifetime, it seems
一生に一度だけプレイすればいいということらしい
Then if it was these 23 fights, it was short-term
では、この23戦だったら短期的だった
Why only fight once in a lifetime
なぜ一生に一度だけ戦うのか
that's a really good question
それは本当に良い質問です
Pneumonia doesn't seem to be just one shot all the time
肺炎は常に1回の発作ではないようです
Because I played it myself, I still need boost
自分でプレイしたのでブーストが必要です
Another problem is that hospital infection
もう一つの問題は院内感染です
Because when my father was 89 years old
というのは父が89歳のとき
never get sick just because it is
だからといって病気になることはありません
Constipation entered the hospital for seven days and left
便秘で7日間入院して退院
The final result is nosocomial infection
最終的な結果は院内感染です
Then we ask that your ward be cleaned again for me.
それでは、あなたの病棟をもう一度掃除していただくようお願いいたします。
or what can we do
あるいは私たちに何ができるでしょうか
It was our doctor who brought the bacteria
細菌を持ち込んだのは私たちの医師でした
No, I think the bacteria was already in the hospital.
いいえ、細菌はすでに病院にいたと思います。
Because of that bacteria, look, you're in the hospital
その細菌のせいで、ほら、あなたは病院にいる​​のよ
You sterilize, and then everyone brings the bacteria in
あなたが滅菌すると、みんなが細菌を持ち込むことになる
And then the bacterium is its genetic material that gets passed around
そして、細菌はその遺伝物質として周囲に伝わります。
Then you and your disinfection is to make it have the power of evolution
そして、あなたとあなたの消毒は、進化の力を持たせることです
Right, so it evolves more and more powerful
そう、どんどん進化して強くなるのです
It if you kill 99% of the bacteria
99％の細菌を死滅させることができれば、
You still survive in large numbers, it's even stronger
あなたはまだ多数で生き残っています、それはさらに強力です
I don't know if the health insurance has statistics
健康保険に統計があるかどうかは知りません
How many elderly people died of hospital infection
院内感染で何人の高齢者が亡くなったのか
We would also like to have such public information to allow
また、そのような公開情報も提供したいと考えています。
We patients know that I am old
私たち患者は私が年をとったことを知っています
Should I go to the hospital or not?
病院に行くべきでしょうか、行かないほうがいいのでしょうか？
or how
あるいはどうやって
What's the reason to go to the hospital
病院に行く理由は何ですか
Can you make your delivery a little longer?
納期をもう少し延ばしてもらえますか？
this is one
これは 1 つです
you're sick of course you want to go to the hospital
もちろん病気です、病院に行きたいです
What about going to the hospital?
病院に行ったらどうでしょうか？
Afraid of nosocomial infection
院内感染が怖い
what do you do
職業はなんですか
this is a good question
これは良い質問です
I don't know what the doctor will decide
医者がどう判断するか分からない
Or to become a style news
あるいはスタイルニュースになる
I sometimes think so
時々そう思います
i've been thinking about this
私はこれについて考えてきました
because sometimes you have to decide
時々決断しなければならないから
what medicine do you take
何の薬を飲んでいますか
Because you want to see what bacteria
何の菌か知りたいから
what medicine
何の薬
doctor he has
彼がいる医者
so i always feel like saying
だからいつも言いたくなるんだ
in this hospital
この病院では
nosocomial infection bacteria
院内感染菌
should be announced
発表されるべきだ
Then sometimes if you have to decide what bacteria
次に、どの細菌を決定する必要がある場合がありますか?
it may be days before you find out
それがわかるまでには数日かかるかもしれない
This patient may have left
この患者は去ったかもしれない
So I've always wondered if there's a way to do a quick quick screening
それで、私はいつも簡単なクイックスクリーンを実行する方法があるかどうか疑問に思っていました
can determine what bacteria it is
それが何の細菌であるかを判断できます
Then we quickly dose
それからすぐに投与します
it's possible to bring it back
持ち帰ることは可能です
this is what i don't know
これは私が知らないことです
I have been wondering if there is a better way
もっと良い方法はないかとずっと考えていました
I would like to add a little bit to the issue of nosocomial infection
院内感染の問題について少し補足したいと思います。
Nosocomial infection actually involves two parts
院内感染には実際には 2 つの部分が含まれます
One is the use of antibiotics
一つは抗生物質の使用です
the resistance it produces
それが生み出す抵抗
The other one, of course, is the patient's resistance
もう一つは、もちろん患者の抵抗です。
So the question asked by this partner just now
それで、今このパートナーが尋ねた質問は
If you want to announce this part
この部分を発表したい場合
It is actually on the one hand
それは実際には一方では
In fact, there is not that high evidence that
実際には、それほど高い証拠はありません
Which bacteria is actually causing
実際にどの細菌が原因なのか
Because of the drug that caused the infection and even caused death
感染症を引き起こし、死に至ることもあった薬のせいで
reason because if he really would cause death
理由は、もし彼が本当に死をもたらすなら
He may be the so-called cluster infection
いわゆる集団感染かもしれない
instead of just one or two patients dying from this bacterium
この細菌によって死亡する患者は 1 人か 2 人ではなく、
So it involves his personal immunity
したがって、それは彼の個人的な免疫に関係します
So this is what he wants to pursue
これが彼が追求したいことなのです
Going back to medical reasons, he may have many layers
医学的理由に戻ると、彼には多くの層があるかもしれません
Reducing nosocomial infections is like what the teacher, Mr. Wu, just said
院内感染を減らすというのは、先ほど呉さんがおっしゃったとおりです。
In fact, hand washing is a very important key step
実際、手洗いは非常に重要な重要なステップです
How to cut off or wear a mask in the hospital
病院内でのマスクの切り方・着用方法
Avoid direct infections on the nose and mouth
鼻や口への直接感染を避ける
These are the basics, that is to say, you can do it yourself in the hospital.
これらは基本的なもので、つまり病院で自分で行うことができます。
Then we patients have to protect ourselves when we go in.
そして、私たち患者は病院に入るときに自分の身を守らなければなりません。
Probably such a situation
たぶんそういう状況
Thanks
ありがとう
Today is live
今日はライブです
So there are already viewers asking questions
すでに視聴者から質問が来ています
ask questions to everyone
みんなに質問する
you see a lot of fans
たくさんのファンに会いますね
One question is how the longan is added to the protein
1つの疑問は、リュウガンがどのようにしてタンパク質に加えられるのかということです。
is your profession
あなたの職業は何ですか
How to add sugar to protein
プロテインに糖を加える方法
very simple
とてもシンプルな
he added to the protein
彼はプロテインを加えた
He has specific mainly two places
彼は具体的に主に2つの場所を持っています
Two kinds of security
2種類のセキュリティ
how to add sugar how to add
砂糖の加え方 加え方
that candy
あのキャンディー
don't recognize you help me answer
認識できません、答えてください
no no no no added to protein what is
いいえ、いいえ、いいえ、プロテインに追加されたものは何ですか
I didn't know this guy is sometimes your specialty
この男が時々あなたの専門分野であるとは知りませんでした
This is added in this Guoju Paris
これはこのGuoju Parisに追加されました
this his problem is
これが彼の問題です
Yes, I don’t know how it is added in the cells
はい、セルにどのように追加されるかわかりません
how to add in the cell
セルに追加する方法
I don't know what the problem is
何が問題なのか分かりません
What is added in the high-vision body
ハイビジョンボディに追加されたもの
yes the question is
はい、質問は
How to add it in the cell
セルに追加する方法
That's what you just mentioned
それがあなたが今言ったことです
Hook and squeeze
引っかけて絞る
Guo Ju Paris
グオ・ジュ・パリ
pick up
選び出す
on the ER
ERで
What about answering?
答えるのはどうでしょうか？
rely on eyebrows
眉毛に頼る
by eyebrow
眉毛で
Yep
はい
if it's chemistry
化学なら
chemical words
化学単語
chemical basis
化学的根拠
yes yes go to the basics
はいはい、基本に戻ります
right
右
Yeah
うん
yes but
はい、でも
It's not that simple if you're using chemistry
化学を使用する場合、それはそれほど単純ではありません
like we just said
先ほど言ったように
If you want to fight, give it
戦いたいなら、与えてください
It's the conjugate vaccine
結合型ワクチンです
just add
追加するだけです
just to
ただ
we are added
私たちは追加されました
the one above lysine
リジンの上のもの
Like you said
あなたが言ったように
Lighting above
上の照明
Eminogur
エミノグル
Of course there must be something to activate it
もちろんそれを活性化する何かがあるはずです
right
右
Or you can be a Linker
または、リンカーになることもできます
then the sugar is
それなら砂糖は
Generally speaking, we need Linker
一般的に言えば、リンカーが必要です
This Linker chooses
このリンカーが選択するのは、
Very Picky
とてもうるさい
This Linker option cannot
このリンカー オプションでは、
Linker it
リンカーしてください
Antigenetic too high
抗原性が高すぎる
also not
またそうではありません
That is to say, it is easy to produce Antibodyzo
つまり、抗体が産生されやすいのです
many such options
そのようなオプションがたくさんあります
a lot to think about
考えるべきことがたくさんある
well, we're running out of time
さて、時間がなくなりました
thank you
ありがとう
Then we once again thank Wu Zhixiong for his very mentality speech
それから私たちは、呉志雄氏の非常に精神的なスピーチにもう一度感謝します。
The preview I need to make is knowledge miss in June
6月に作る必要のあるプレビューはナレッジミスです
The topic of the talk is Hu Shi and Li Ao
話のテーマは胡石と李蓉です
Interactions Between Two Generations of Liberals in Taiwan
台湾の二世代にわたるリベラル派の交流
Is the keynote speaker of the Huang Kewu Special Research Fellow at the Institute of Modern History
近代史研究所の黄克武特別研究員の基調講演者です
Please sign up to attend this speech
この講演に参加するにはサインアップしてください
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
Thanks
ありがとう